you know when people talk about work
你知道，人们总是谈论工作与
life balance what's your honest opinion
生活的平衡，你对此有什么真实看法？
of that Kobe Bryant wasn't doing three
科比·布莱恩特凌晨三点投三个球肯定不是
throws at 3:00 a.m. for no reason but
无缘无故的，但这肯定是有
there's a cost to that right George
代价的，对吧？乔治·
heeden the founder of global fashion
希登，全球时尚
brand represent warn by the weekend post
品牌Represent的创始人，周末邮报·
Malone Justin Bieber one of the most
马龙和贾斯汀·比伯联名推出的
popular Luxury Street brands in the
全球最受欢迎的奢侈街头品牌之一。
world when I was 18 starting this brand
我18岁创立这个品牌的时候，
it was just me and my brother in my
只有我和我兄弟在我
dad's shed figuring out products and
爸的棚子里琢磨产品，琢磨
where we could take the brand but then
品牌的发展方向。后来，
we went from doing 10 15 sales to like a
我们的销量从每天1万到
th000 every day of the week 2,000 3,000
1.5万件飙升到每天2000、3000、4000件，
4,000 we were making money at that time
我们当时赚的钱比我们
early 20s so we're [__] around a lot
20岁出头应该赚的要多得多。所以我们到处玩乐，
alcohol girls cars and we're doing like
喝酒、泡妞、买车，我们的
35 million revenue and was like we're
收入达到了3500万美元，当时我们想着
going to do 50 million next year but we
明年要达到5000万美元，但我们
we don't know what we're doing now the
不知道自己在做什么。现在，
business is doing about $100 million
公司的年收入已经达到1亿美元左右了。 那时我才
that's when the realization came that
意识到，
you don't need to be good at business to
你不需要擅长经商才能
own a business there's people that are
拥有一家公司。有些人比
so much better at things than you they
你强得多，他们
can lay the foundations for it to become
可以为你的公司打下基础，让它成为
a billion dollar band and you can focus
一家价值十亿美元的公司，而你可以专注于
on what you're actually good at that was
你真正擅长的领域。那份
a car list that just changed everything
清单彻底改变了一切。
we're building this there's no seing to
我们正在打造这个公司，它的未来不可限量。
what it can be that was until we got a
直到我们收到一封信，
from that was the worst day in the
那是公司历史上最糟糕的一天，我们跌到了
business it was rock bottom but the best
谷底。但
view of Heaven is from hell right you've
天堂的最佳视角往往来自地狱，对吧？你
got to get to the bottom of that
必须先跌到
mountain to start re climbing it it
山脚才能重新开始攀登。这
became this driving force that I thought
成为了我的动力，我想，
who cannot stop that and then what
谁能阻止它呢？然后
happens it's absolutely crazy to me that
发生了什么？这对我来说简直太疯狂了，
so many of you have decided to watch our
你们中有这么多人决定观看我们的
show um and so many of you have decided
节目，这么多人决定
to subscribe to our show we now have
订阅我们的节目。我们现在
five million subscribers on YouTube
在YouTube上有500万订阅者，
which is a number that I just can't
这个数字我简直无法
comprehend and it's a dream that I
想象，这完全是我以前想都不敢想的。
absolutely never could have had we
我们
started the dire of a just over 3 years
三年前开始了“Dire of a”项目，
ago now and in my wildest expectations
在我最狂野的预期里，
we might have had 100,000 subscribers by
我们或许只有…… 现在我们已经有10万订阅用户了，
now so you can imagine how shocked I am
所以你们可以想象我有多么惊讶，竟然有这么
that so many of you have chosen to tune
多人选择
into these conversations every week um
每周收听我们的节目，花
and spend some time with us so thank you
时间和我们一起聊天。非常感谢你们！
and I made a deal with you I made a deal
我和你们做了个约定：
that if you subscribed to this show that
如果你们订阅这个节目，
we would continue to raise the bar and
我们会不断提高标准。
2024 we're going to raise the BARC never
2024年，我们将把BARC值提升到
before I've been working for the last
前所未有的高度。过去
nine months on a surprise for all of you
九个月我一直在为所有订阅用户准备一个惊喜，
that have subscribed to the show and I'm
我
very excited to deliver that for you the
非常激动地要把它呈现给大家。节目的
production's going to change we're going
制作方式将会改变，我们会
to go even further with our guests and
和嘉宾进行更深入的交流，
we're going to tell even more Global
讲述更多全球性的
stories so as always if you appreciate
故事。所以，和以往一样，如果你喜欢
what we're doing here the simple free
我们的节目，
favorite I'll ask for you is to hit the
我唯一想请你做的就是点击
Subscribe button let's get on with the
订阅按钮。让我们开始今天的
[Music]
[音乐]
episode
节目吧。
George what is the mission that you're
乔治，你的目标是什么？我的目标是
on it's just to be the best version of
成为最好的
myself really just to show up and do
自己，尽我
everything at the highest level I can
所能做到最好。
what influence did your parents have
你的父母对你有什么影响？
because I I've heard you talk about your
我听你
mother and your father a lot but let's
多次提起你的父母，但我们
start with your father what kind of
先从你的父亲说起吧。
influence did he have on you I guess
他对你有什么影响？我想，在
when I was growing up he had he had a
我成长的过程中，他比
my town so like he had a Range Rover and
镇上其他人拥有的要多一些。比如，他有一辆路虎揽胜，
he dropped me off to school in that
他开着那辆车送我去上学，
Range Rover and all the kids felt that
所有孩子都觉得这
was sick so automatically I felt proud
很酷，所以我自然而然地感到自豪。我当时就想，
of that so I was like I want to be like
我也想成为像他那样的人，
this like what is it that my dad's got
我父亲到底有什么
that other people don't have um and the
别人没有的？还有
way he showed up with my family and how
他对待家人的方式，以及他对待家人的态度。
he would he wouldn't like I I've never
我从没
seen him drunk even to this day I've
见过他喝醉，直到今天也
never seen him drunk like he was a role
没见过。他就像我的
model is like a this stoic guy that
榜样，一个坚忍不拔的人，努力工作，每天
would just work hard show up drop his
送
kids off at school come to football
孩子上学，晚上还来参加足球
training every single night like he
训练。他总是陪伴着
would be there for me and I think that
我。我想，
was just like even though it was never
虽然
spoke about in the household it just
家里人从不谈论这些，但这却
like created my own discipline I guess
培养了我的自律。他是个
was he an emotional man no no no emotion
感情丰富的人吗？不，他一点感情都没有。
I've never seen him cry has he ever said
我从没见过他哭。他有没有说过“
I love
我爱
you to me I don't know maybe as a young
你”？ 我，我不知道，也许小时候是这样，
kid but not not recently now what about
但最近不是了。
your mom very supportive she used to sit
你妈妈很支持你，她以前
on the end of my bed every night and be
每天晚上都坐在我床边，对我说：“
like George you got to make it you got
乔治，你一定要成功，你得
to carry your brother and sister like
照顾好你的弟弟妹妹，
you've got you've got to carry this
你得扛起这个
family on which was quite a hard thing
家。”这话
to take in when I was young um but she
我小时候很难接受，但她
just like affirmed that every single day
每天都这样鼓励我，
and like she loved the work I did and
她喜欢我的作品和
the art that I did and she would try and
艺术，她会
express that to all her friends and talk
跟她的朋友们说，经常谈论
about me a lot and it was always like
我。
of um it kind of pushed me a bit you
这就像是一种鼓励，
know gave gave me like words of words of
给了我很多
affirmation I guess confidence was that
肯定的话语，让我更有自信。
was her saying that like a frequent
她经常这么说，
thing I'm just trying to figure out why
我只是想知道为什么
she would say that to you versus your
她会这样对你而不是对你的
siblings is presumably because you're
兄弟姐妹，大概是因为
you're the oldest no I was a middle
你是老大吧？不，我是老二，比
child brother's old um but Mike kind
弟弟大，但迈克
younger kid and um didn't come out much
小时候比较内向，不太爱出风头，
and he just did his own thing whereas I
他总是做自己的事，而我
would express myself a little bit more
会表达自己。
than him in within the family and I
在家里，我比他稍微更有影响力一些，我
think my mom saw that as a way that I
觉得我妈妈认为这能让我将来
could be the the carrier of whatever
成为家族事业的继承人。
your parents what did they do so your
你父母是做什么的？你
dad was my dad sold mini buses so him
爸爸，我爸爸是卖小巴的，他
and his his dad were in business so that
和他爷爷一起做生意，这有点像
was kind of like me and my brother and
我和我哥哥，我们俩长得一样，做着
same they did the same thing like had
一样的事，举止
the same demeanor same attitude to
神态也一样，对
everything and I think that's why me and
所有事情的态度都一样。我想这就是我和
my brother went into business cuz we saw
我哥哥后来也做生意的原因，因为我们看到
that the family had been able to do that
家族企业能够做到这一点。
um prior did you have any idea when you
嗯，在你12、13、14岁的时候，你有没有想过
were a young man like 12 13 14 that you
自己会进入
would be in this
这个
industry yeah I did to be fair looking
行业？是的，说实话，我的确想过。
back at it I I had sensitive skin as a
我小时候皮肤很敏感，
kid and anything that fit me wrong or
任何不合身的衣服，或者让我
like itched me or like like a back neck
发痒的衣服，比如后领的
label or the way a pant fit would
标签，或者裤子的版型，都会让
irritate me so much that I'd take it to
我非常难受，所以我会拿去给
my Grands and she was a tailor so she
我奶奶，她是个裁缝，她
would taper things and take necks out of
会帮我把衣服改窄，把领子改小，
things and she would make sure I knew
而且她还会确保我知道衣服的
what the composition was before buying
成分。 买
garments and when I look back at it now
衣服，现在回想起来，
I realized that that being that
我意识到，
particular so young kind of stemmed into
年少时那种对服装的执着，某种程度上影响了
how I've built the brand and what it
我后来建立品牌的方式，以及品牌所代表的理念、
stands for and the quality and
品质等等。
everything like that and Michael I met
迈克尔，我之前见过他，第一次你
had you on the podcast I think you had
上播客的时候，我记得你当时有
eight employees and Michael was there as
八个员工，迈克尔也在。
well yeah and he comes across as a bit
他给人的感觉有点像个
of a genius but a bit of a introverted
天才，但又有点内向。
genius what was the difference in your
你们的技能有什么区别？
skill set cuz you both went and studied
因为你们都学过
like art well graphic design what was
艺术，或者说平面设计。
the difference in your skill set there
你们的技能有什么不同？
wasn't really one he was just better
其实没什么区别，他只是
than me okay better than me at Art
比我强。好吧，艺术方面肯定比我强。
definitely and cuz he was my big brother
因为他是我哥哥，
I looked up to him so like through
我一直很崇拜他。从
Primary School like he was into like
小学开始，他就喜欢
heavy metal and rock and like California
重金属、摇滚、加州风情、
and surf and skate and that wasn't
冲浪和滑板。
really a particular thing in Bolton like
在博尔顿，这些并不常见，
everyone was in tracksuits and had
大家都穿着运动服，剃着
shaped heads and tiens and smoked on the
寸头，戴着Tiens的帽子，在
corner we were skating down these cobbly
街角抽烟。我们却穿着
roads with long hair and like big DC
长发，穿着厚底DC
shoes on and skinny jeans and I I just
鞋和紧身牛仔裤，在鹅卵石路上滑板。我一直
wanted to be him like until like early
都想成为他，直到……
20s like he was he was my idol really
他二十多岁的时候，真的是我的偶像。
and when did um when did you make the
你是什么时候
decision to apply your artistic skills
决定把你的艺术才能运用
to clothing college so we had a project
到服装设计上的？当时我们有个项目，要用
something of our art that could sell and
我们的艺术作品做一些可以卖的东西。
Mike had Mike was two years ahead of me
迈克比我高两届，
so he'd already done the same course I
所以他已经完成了和我一样的课程，
was on and he'd done like a little
他还开了一个小
Gallery where people would buy his
画廊，人们在那里买他的
drawings and I looked at that and I
画作。我看了看，又
looked at my dad and my dad wanted us to
看了看我爸，我爸当时想让我们也做这
come into the business at the time and
行，
but also I didn't want to sit and wait
但我最不想做的就是这个。而且我也不想一辈子坐等
around all my life to sell a painting
一幅画卖
for 40 grand um and I remember going
四万英镑。我记得
into the class and I remember the
走进教室，
teacher telling me that average salary
老师告诉我平面
of a graphic designer was 30k and I'd go
设计师的平均年薪是三万英镑。我回家后跟
home and I'd speak to my dad I'd be like
我爸说，
hold on if University is going to cost
等等，如果大学
me 9k a year and the average salary is
一年要花九千英镑，而平均年薪只有
40k a year and like I can't [__] buy
四万英镑，那我连辆路虎揽胜都买不起。
and I wanted to be like my dad so I was
我想成为像我爸那样的人。 我当时就在想，
like what what is it that I can make
我能做什么来
that I can make money from like everyone
赚钱呢？每个人
wants to be successful right there's no
都想成功，对吧？不可否认，
thing back then that I wanted and I was
那时候钱对我来说非常重要。我非常渴望成功，而且我对
so particular about the clothing like I
服装的要求很高，就像我之前
said about my grand and taking things in
说的，我特别注重服装的合身度，
and how we'd adjust all my garments that
以及我们如何调整我的衣服。那时候
upbringing of social media Instagram was
社交媒体
just starting and YouTube was just
刚刚兴起，Instagram 和 YouTube 也刚刚
starting and I I I managed to watch a
出现。我设法看了
few videos of like artists like shepher
几个艺术家的视频，比如 Shepher
Ferry who owned o and Nikki diamonds who
Ferry（O 的创始人）和 Nikki Diamonds（
own Diamond Supply and huff and these
Diamond Supply 和 Huff 的创始人），还有一些
guys over here on the West Coast that
西海岸的艺术家，他们
were just selling like t-shirts with
卖印有图案的 T 恤。
graphics on and I thought why can't we
我想，为什么我们不能也这样做呢？我们能
do we be the British version of that
成为英国版的他们吗？
what have we got to do to do that and
我们该怎么做才能做到这一点？
second ago you said being a graphic
后来，我遇到了一个大学项目，就想，不如试试看。你知道，你刚才说，做平面
designer wasn't going to allow you to
设计师并不能让你
buy the same car as your dad was how
买得起和你爸爸一样的车。那么，
much was your dad a driving force behind
你爸爸在
um your decision- making and like when I
你做决定的时候，对你的影响有多大呢？就像我
say that like was there really a
说的…… 就像，你真的有
motivation to try and beat him or at
动力去打败他，或者
least get to where he was yeah
至少达到他的高度吗？是的，
definitely definitely and a very
绝对是，而且是非常
conscious motivation
自觉的动力。是的，
yeah and because you thought that make
因为你觉得那样能让
him proud or make yourself proud yeah I
他骄傲，或者让自己骄傲。是的，我
thought it'd make the family proud but
觉得那样会让家人骄傲。但同时，
in my family that or even through my
我的家人，甚至我的
friends or through my mom and dad's
朋友，我父母的
friends whoever was around us no one
朋友，所有在我们身边的人，都没人
thought that we'd ever be anything no
想到我们会取得这样的成就。没
one thought that like our art could s
人想到我们的艺术可以成功，
and we could make money that way and we
我们可以靠艺术赚钱，我们
could build careers that way everyone
可以靠艺术建立事业。每个人都
always expected us especially my grand
期望我们，尤其是我的祖父，
just expected us to go into the family
期望我们继承
business having listened to some of your
家业。听过你的一些
interviews and stuff and gotten to know
采访，也了解了
you it does feel like there's a bit of a
你，感觉你有点
chip on your shoulder and I'm not
耿耿于怀。我
necessarily sure who the chip on your
不确定你的这种耿耿于怀来自哪里，我觉得
shoulder has come from I think a lot of
很大程度上是
it self-inflicted I think I just like to
自己造成的。我想我只是喜欢
have something there to prove something
有东西可以证明一些事情是
wrong or something right maybe Pro
错的，或者一些事情是对的。也许证明
myself right comes at a cost though it
自己是对的，是要付出代价的，确实要付出代价。是的，
does come at a cost yeah but I'm willing
但我愿意
to take that cost on are you sure yeah
承担这个代价。你确定吗？是的，我愿意。 我已经
I've I've been doing it now for 13 years
做了13年了，
I'm not going to stop anytime soon and
短期内不会停下来。
like I only feel now that we're just
我现在感觉才刚刚
getting started with it so I'm really
起步，所以我
curious about this early phase which I
对这个早期阶段非常好奇，我
kind of call the shedding phase where an
称之为“蜕变阶段”。在这个阶段，
entrepreneur makes the decision that
创业者决定在他们现有的社交圈中
they're going to do something unusual in
做一些不同寻常的事情。
group and the shedding phase I Define as
我把“蜕变阶段”定义为：
like when your family start thinking
你的家人开始觉得
you're a bit weird and you feel the
你有点怪，你感受到
resistance from your family and then
来自家人的阻力，然后
you're like boys from school start
学校里的男生开始觉得
thinking you think you're Richard
你觉得自己是理查德·
Branson or whatever and they start
布兰森之类的，他们开始
making little comments can you recount
说些闲话。你能回忆一下
what your shedding facee was like I
你蜕变时的表情吗？我
think that was it I think like a lot of
想就是那样。我觉得当时
people who was around just laughed at it
周围的很多人都觉得好笑，觉得
a lot of people just thought it was a
这只是个
joke and it got to that stage where then
玩笑。后来，人们开始说：“
it was like oh it's your dad's business
哦，这是你爸爸的生意，
your dad's your dad buys the stock and
你爸爸的，你爸爸买股票，
like like this is a family business you
这是家族企业，你们
guys aren't making this money and
赚不到这么多钱。”
whatever until it gets to a point where
等等。直到它发展到一定程度，
it like just completely exceeds what
远远超出
people think that is and then they seem
人们的预期，然后他们似乎……
to come back around and then they buying
他们会回头，然后买
your product and then they're
你的产品，然后
congratulating you on the drops and then
祝贺你产品上市，然后
they're your biggest fans do you
他们就成了你最大的粉丝。你还
remember any comments that you heard oh
记得听到过什么评论吗？哦，
from C people yeah definitely I remember
来自C的人，当然记得。我记得有一次，
there was one where I'd bought this R8
我买了一辆R8，当时
and it was I must have been 19 or 20
我大概19、20岁，
which is a car right right yeah and an
那是一辆车，对吧？对，是辆
Audi and um I it packed up in in my town
奥迪。嗯，它在我住的镇上抛锚了。
where I was and I remember getting a
我记得
message on Facebook
在Facebook上收到一条消息，
saying that car your dad's bought you is
说你爸爸给你买的车
packed up here he's going to get a
抛锚了，他要因为压
ticket on them yellow lines and I was
黄线被罚款了。我当时
thinking like come on how did it make
想，拜托，
you feel it made me want to go to the
你当时是什么感觉？这让我想要在各方面都更上一层楼，一遍又一遍地重复，以此来
to so it drown out that noise so it was
盖过那些噪音。所以我想，
like okay maybe his dad was
好吧，也许他爸爸很
successful running a a small business
成功，经营着一家小公司，有一套
had a a nice house and whatever I wanted
漂亮的房子什么的，但我想要
to take that to like a hundred times
把这些都提升一百倍，
that to prove that it wasn't that I
来证明事实并非如此。所以，在
guess and so after you leave College
你大学毕业之后，嗯，其实是在
well it's during college right when you
大学期间，你
sort of start the business MH is that
开始创业的时候，MH，那是
2012 yeah when you first started the
2012年吗？是的，你刚开始
business and then Michael joins you a
创业的时候。然后是Michael
year later after you started selling
一年后，在你开始卖
T-shirts yeah he was doing a bit of the
T恤之后，他加入了你。是的，他当时负责一些零散的
graphics here and there and um I would
图案设计，我会把订单送到
office and then at night would sit and
邮局，然后晚上我们会一起坐下来
draw together and then I'd speak to
画图，之后我会和
suppliers in China and stuff like that
中国的供应商联系等等，就这样一直持续到
three years that I was at University
我上大学的那三年。
what was that first year like that first
第一年，也就是
year in business uh from what I can
创业的第一年，嗯，就我
remember it wasn't really business it
记忆所及，那其实不算真正的创业，就是
was just going to The Back Garden where
去
my dad shed was speak to some suppliers
我爸的后花园（也就是他的棚子所在的地方），和中国的供应商联系，
in China go to university complete my
去大学完成
whatever it was I was doing there come
我的学业，
back pack orders speak to customers do
回来打包订单，和客户沟通，如此循环往复，持续了
the first three years how big was the
三年。
business in the first year probably
第一年生意规模有多大？大概营业额
turned over about 10,000 pounds yeah
1万英镑吧。
what about the second year
第二年呢？
um maybe like 50k I think the third year
大概5万英镑吧。我想第三年
is when we decided to actually make it a
我们决定
limited company and get an accountant
正式成立有限公司，并聘请了会计。
and how much did you do in the third
第三
year roughly in terms of Revenue I can't
年你们的收入大概是多少？我
remember I think it was around half a
记不清了，我想大概是50万英镑左右吧。
mill okay because I remember going to
好的，因为我记得……
the accountants and we we did all this
会计师们，我们做了所有这些，
um we literally like T the business
我们真的把公司彻底
apart and rebuilt it and he said to us
拆解重建了。最后，他对我们说，
at the end of this thing like if you've
如果你们
got 100 Grand in the bank you should
银行里有10万英镑，就应该
carry on with it if not you've spent
继续做下去，否则你们白白浪费了
three years just like doing nothing and
三年时间，毫无进展。
it's going nowhere and uh luckily we had
幸运的是，我们
way more than that in the bank and it's
银行里的钱远远不止这些，所以我们就想，
was like okay let's let's do this for
好吧，让我们认真做下去。
real you spent two years you know and by
你知道，你花了两年时间，到
the end of the second year you're
第二年年底才
generating 50k which is like not enough
赚了5万英镑，这根本不够
really to pay yourself a salary whilst
支付自己的工资和
covering costs of the business no I
公司运营成本。不，我
didn't take a salary for seven or eight
七八年都没拿过工资，
years so surely that Point people around
所以你周围的人肯定都
you are telling you that you're an idiot
在说你是个傻瓜，
and they've got quite good evidence yeah
他们也确实有充分的证据
to suggest that you're actually wasting
证明你是在浪费
your time but I I never had never had a
时间。但我从来没有真正
big doubt that it wouldn't work I've had
怀疑过它会失败。我有
a lot of doubts but never had a doubt
很多疑虑，但从未怀疑过
that it wouldn't work and I knew that I
它会失败，我知道我会尽
would do everything I could to make sure
我所能确保
it worked what did work how would you
它成功。 当时真正奏效的是什么？你如何
define worked at that that moment like
定义“奏效”？当时的
what was success at that moment success
成功是什么？成功
was putting products online and it
就是把产品上线
selling and seeing that launch night and
销售，看到产品发布当晚有
seeing 500 people log in and buy
500人登录购买，
something or a thousand people and
或者1000人登录购买，
seeing that incremental gain over time
看到用户数量随着时间推移稳步增长。这才是真正的
that was what was like the driving force
驱动力：
more people following the brand more
更多人关注品牌，更多
people sending DMS that that was it
人发送私信。就是这样。那么，
really why don't people start and I say
为什么人们不开始呢？我这么说是因为，事后回想起来，
you're going to understand looking back
你会明白的。回顾你
at your own work the quality of it what
自己的工作，看看它的质量，想想
like and as well wasting time if they've
你经历过什么，你可能已经很清楚为什么人们不开始。你肯定收到过很多私信，人们都有想法，比如时尚创意或其他什么，为什么不开始呢？我认为是失败的压力，是怀疑的感觉，还有浪费时间。如果他们
got a family or they've got a job where
有家庭或者全职工作，就没时间
it's full-time then to start something
去做
else on the side when they've got to see
其他事情了。他们要照顾
to the family or the girlfriend or the
家人、女朋友、
wife or whatever it is like you don't
妻子等等，根本没有
have much time to go and do something
时间去做
else that you then hope will eventually
其他事情。 然后你就会希望它最终能
in the future take off or become
在未来腾飞或获得
successful and it takes so long like it
成功，但这需要很长时间，真的需要很长时间。
does take I know it's a lot of people
我知道很多人
say takes 10 years to become an overan
都说
night success and I think that's true
一夜成名需要十年时间，我觉得这话没错。
you you spent almost four years um from
你花了将近四年时间，嗯，从
2012 till I guess no two years 2012 till
2012年到，不，应该是两年，大概从2012年到
about 2015 is kind of just effectively
2015年，基本上就是瞎
messing around yeah messing around
摸索，对，瞎摸索，
really messing around a lot of messing
真的瞎摸索，摸索了很多，
around learning learning yeah is
学习，学习，嗯，用“学习”这个
probably a better better use of words
词可能更贴切，
and enjoying it as well like me and my
而且也乐在其中。我和我的
friends had sit in my dad's shed like
朋友们经常在我爸爸的棚子里坐一
all night just figuring out products and
整夜，琢磨产品，琢磨
things that we wanted to do and where we
我们想做什么，以及我们
could take the brand and I'd love to go
能把品牌发展到什么程度。我很想回到那段时光，
back to them times cuz they were great
因为那段时光很棒，
and we had nothing and no one was really
我们一无所有，也没人真正
watching us but we thought everyone was
关注我们，但我们觉得每个人都在
watching us and we thought it was the
关注我们，我们觉得我们会成为
next big [__] Powerhouse of a
下一个超级大
brand um so yeah it was it was fun like
品牌。嗯，是的，那段时光很有趣，
I don't regret any of it you know what
我一点也不后悔。你知道吗，
putting these two questions together
把这两个问题放在一起，一个是
about like why people don't start and
为什么人们不开始，
also those three years where you weren't
另一个是那三年。 你当时
really making any any money yeah um and
根本没赚到什么钱，嗯，
you in the shed in your GR in your dad's
你在你爸家的棚子里，
why didn't you quit because as I said a
你为什么不辞职呢？就像我刚才说的，
second ago there must have been so much
肯定有很多
force telling you to go and get a real
声音在劝你去找份正经
job yeah but why didn't you quit I think
工作，是啊，但你为什么不辞职呢？我觉得
it just leads back to again proving
这又回到了证明
people wrong and proving myself right
别人错了，证明自己是对的这个问题上。
and like the only other option I had was
我唯一的选择就是
to go and work for my dad and I didn't
去帮我爸干活，但我不想那样，
want to do that because I'd done that
因为我
all my teens and I hated it I hated
整个青少年时期都在干，我讨厌那份工作。我讨厌
cleaning mini buses and ripping stickers
洗小巴，讨厌撕掉窗户上的贴纸，讨厌去
auctions and bidding on cars and stuff
拍卖会竞拍汽车之类的，那
like that wasn't me and that was the
不是我，但那是
only other option I had so it was like
我唯一的选择。所以，要么就这样，要么就什么都不是。
really when you look back at the uh
回头看看
products that you made in that shed how
你在棚子里做的那些产品，
do you feel about them there was a few
你对它们有什么感觉？有一些
great ones and a few absolutely terrible
很棒的，也有一些非常糟糕的。
ones I remember the first collection I
我记得我的第一个系列，我
moved to China because originally I
搬到了中国，因为一开始我
would buy stocking from America print it
会从美国买袜子，
in the UK and like make zero profit on
在英国印刷，然后…… 虽然零利润，
it but it was great and it felt great
但感觉很棒，也很棒。
and then eventually we decided like
后来我们决定
let's try and make some profit on a on a
尝试做一个
collection and I remember this
系列来盈利。我记得
collection coming back after a few
几个月后，这个系列又回来了，
months and like all the fits were wrong
所有的版型
and the Fabrics were wrong and I I just
和面料都不对。那天晚上，我在
cried on my mom's floor for like hours
妈妈家的地板上哭了几个小时。
that night um so there was there was a
所以，那段
lot of really rough times as well there
时间确实很艰难，但也有
was a lot of fun but it was all just
很多乐趣。一切都像是在
like figuring out different things and
摸索各种事情，
like learning how to do every single job
学习如何做好这个行业里的每一项工作。
within that business because you know if
你知道，如果
I'm a young fashion designer or a young
我是一个年轻的时装设计师或
creative and I look at your work now I
创意人员，当我看到你现在的作品，
look at the product that represents
看到你
putting out now it's easy to see how one
现在推出的产品时，很容易理解为什么有人会因此而
might be put off from starting right
放弃。
because I look at yourself Jesus Christ
因为我看着你，我的天哪，你会觉得
like you can't compete with it you can't
你根本无法与之竞争，你根本无法与之
compete with that like that's more than
竞争，那可是超过
10 years of like Mastery so I'm just not
十年的精湛技艺，所以我
going to bother starting what what do
干脆就不开始了。
you say to those people say look you got
你会对这些人说什么呢？告诉他们，你必须
to put the work in it's going to be 10
付出努力，这需要十年的时间，
years like regardless of what industry
无论在哪个行业都是如此。
it is or what product you're making like
你做的产品，
I wouldn't even think about the next two
我甚至都不会考虑未来两
to three years I'd think about 10 years
三年，我会考虑十年。
like that's the mindset you've got to
你必须要有这种心态。这
have and and it's not going to be easy
并不容易，也不
and it's not going to be fun but you
容易，但你必须竭尽全力去
make it work so the brand kind of scales
实现它，让品牌规模扩大。
to what sort of Revenue number from 2012
从2012年到
up to 2018 we built it up to like 6 to 7
2018年，我们的营收达到了600万到700
mil MH so like 2015 16 17 it was just
万美元。2015、2016、2017年，营收基本持平，
flat like 6 7 mil year over year yeah
每年都在600万到700万美元之间。
at the at the time as our young s we not
当时我们认为这就是上限了，因为我们年轻，缺乏
knowledge and no real thought in the
知识和经验。 当时
industry like we thought that we were at
我们觉得，在行业里，我们已经达到了
the ceiling of what represent was and
Represent品牌的极限。
then that's when the realization came
然后我们意识到，
that like if we carry on doing what
如果我们继续做现在做的事情，行不通了，
work and this brand will fail what was
这个品牌会失败。
the advice you needed at that point that
你当时需要什么建议，而
you didn't get um I definitely didn't
你没有得到？嗯，我确实没有
get the advice but it was to just
得到建议，但关键是要
completely restart refocus go again
彻底重新开始，重新聚焦，再次
build a new team and and and go into
组建团队，然后去做
what we already knew that was there
我们早已知道的事情——那些一直在那里
waiting for us we knew what we were
等着我们的事情。我们知道自己有
capable of we just weren't doing it what
能力做什么，只是没有去做。你当时没有做什么？
weren't you doing focusing on our
专注于我们的
consumer asking them what they wanted
消费者，询问他们想要什么，与
speaking to them being within the
他们交流，融入
community of what represent was and
Represent的社群，并满足他们的需求。你提到了
say the the point about team MH um you
MH团队，嗯，你
said rebuild a new team when you started
说要重建一个新团队。在你创立
the brand who did who were you hiring
这个品牌的时候，你雇佣了谁？你雇佣的都是
all my
我的
friends I hired all my friends all my
朋友，我雇佣了我所有的朋友，我所有
close friends cuz I wanted to enjoy it
亲密的朋友，因为我想享受这个过程，我当时
and I didn't know think about hiring
并不了解招聘，
people I didn't want to interview people
我不想面试候选人，也不想把
and bring them into my dad's garden shed
他们带到我爸爸的花园小屋里。
so up until we had a unit like it was
所以，在我们拥有自己的工作室之前，
just me and my friends and we were all
只有我和我的朋友们。 我们当时每个人都
just doing 50 jobs each no one had a
身兼50个工作，没人有
title no one knew what was going on um
头衔，没人知道发生了什么，嗯，结果并不理想。
and it didn't work but now we're at such
但现在我们已经发展到
a level where there's a hundred people
一百人的规模，
that came in right at the start are
当初加入的两位朋友现在
still in the business and a very high up
仍然在公司，而且身居要职，
in the business and have amazing
拥有令人艳羡的
successful lives so half worked and half
成功人生。所以一半成功了，一半失败了。
didn't when you say it didn't work what
你说失败了，这到底
does that mean in reality it means that
意味着什么？实际上，这意味着……
like we I guess it's all not my fault as
我想这并非完全是我的错，
such but it's all
而是因为
it's I I brought people into the brand
我把一些
that shouldn't have been in fashion or
不适合时尚圈的人招进了公司，或者说，
shouldn't have been doing what I'd asked
我让
them to do or like their career didn't
他们做的工作并不适合他们，或者他们的职业生涯并没有按照预期发展。
because we were just just Plateau at
因为当时我们只是在一个
like a a quite a boring fashion brand at
相当平庸的时尚品牌的基层停滞不前，所以
the time and like did we had to split up
我们不得不分崩离析，重新
and we had to regroup and start again
集结，一切从头开始。那些
and the ones that stayed have now stayed
留下来的人一直都在，这简直
forever which is insane and the ones
不可思议；而那些
that left they've have' carried on with
离开的人也继续着
their lives what have you learned about
他们的生活。你从中吸取了哪些关于
um hiring again when I say the advice
招聘的经验教训？ 再说一遍，
that you might give if you could speak
如果你能和
to George at 18 years old and you could
18岁的乔治对话，并就如何
give hiring advice on how to pick people
挑选人才给出一些建议，你会说
what would you say hire Fast Fire faster
什么？你会说“快速招聘，火力全开”吗？很
interesting I spent a lot of years
有意思。我曾经有好几年
where I didn't hire people because I
没招人，因为我
didn't think they would fit into the
觉得他们不适合我们的
brand and even though they don't seem a
品牌。即使他们看起来不太像某种
certain way or they're into the same
类型，或者他们喜欢和
brands that I'm into or they follow this
我一样的品牌，或者他们从事
kind of um industry that we're in
我们所在的行业——
whether it's streetware or luxury or
无论是街头服饰、奢侈品还是
high fashioned like there is still
高级时装——仍然有很多
unbelievable people that can do amazing
非常优秀的人，他们能做出
things way better than what can do in
远超常人的惊人成就，无论在
all levels of business that don't look
哪个层面，即使他们看起来不像是合适的人。所以，如果
that back back then would have really
当时我能意识到这一点，真的会对
helped the business
公司的
grow I think sometimes like young
发展大有帮助。我觉得，像年轻的
Founders um I remember just thinking
创始人，
sometimes scared to hire people that are
有时候会害怕招聘比
like more experienced than we are
我们更有经验的人，
because how are we going to manage them
因为我们不知道该如何管理他们，等等。
why would they want to come here you
他们为什么要来这里？你
know why would they want to come here
知道吗？他们为什么要来这里
was a massive thing for me really yeah
对我来说确实是个大问题。是啊，
why would want why would someone want to
为什么会有人想
come to a smaller brand than what they
加入一个比他们之前所在的公司规模还小的品牌呢？
were at um and especially in that time
尤其是在公司发展停滞不前的时候，因为
when it wasn't growing cuz it's not you
谁都
don't want to go into a company that's
不想加入一家
not growing but like now it's completely
没有发展的公司。但现在情况完全
different the the whole ecosystem that
不同了，我们建立的整个生态系统，
we've built and who wants to come into
以及那些想要加入
the brand and like the way the brand is
这个品牌的人，都让我们眼花缭乱。现在，
growing it's now like we have the
我们
it's hard to pick and choose who we
很难挑选合适的人加入，而不是像以前那样到处
out there and looking for them and
寻找人才，
trying to get them into brand you know
努力把他们招进来。你明白
what I mean mhm it's so like Catch 22
我的意思吗？嗯，这就像一个悖论。
you know I have a lot of dragon Den
你知道，我有很多“龙穴”
Investments and these are typically
投资项目，这些通常都是处于
early stage companies that often quite
早期阶段、非常
young and I sit with them all the time
年轻的公司。我经常和他们坐在一起，
and I I talk to them about this Paradox
和他们讨论这个悖论。这是
of um there it's some kind of
一个
multifaceted thing they are a very young
多方面的问题，他们非常年轻。
team very inexperienced they have small
团队经验不足，
budgets relatively small budgets so
预算也比较少，所以
they're thinking we can't pay an
他们觉得我们请不起
exceptional really experienced person
真正经验丰富的优秀人才，
because £1,000 salary is so much for us
因为1000英镑的年薪对我们来说太多了。而且就像
stuff you said about like why would
你说的，为什么会
anyone want to come work in this like
有人想来这里工作？
shed right because of that they never
正因为如此，他们才无法
grow to be able to pay for those people
发展到能够支付得起这些人的薪水，也无法
to be able to create an environment
创造一个吸引
where exceptional people would come
优秀人才的环境。
right so the only way like I see of
所以，我认为
kickstarting the process is to bring in
启动这个过程的唯一方法就是
exceptional people now um yeah that
现在就引进优秀人才。嗯，这很
makes sense pay for it now and you'll
有道理，现在投入资金，
see the increased outcome later
以后肯定会看到成效。
definitely yeah yeah like bringing in
引进
exceptional people will never be a bad
优秀人才
thing in the business but it feels like
对企业来说永远都不是坏事，但感觉上好像是坏事，
it because they they because it costs so
因为成本太高了。
much so much yeah yeah but you're also
但是你也会从
going to learn so much from them just
他们身上学到很多东西，
especially if you're a small team and
特别是如果你是一个小团队，
you're bringing in people that have been
引进那些已经在
in there for 10 years and done what
这里工作了10年，并且做过
you're trying to do like the in the
你正在做的事情的人，
information and the value that they
他们提供的信息和价值会让
provide just to open your mind up to
你大开眼界，让你看到
what's actually possible can get you to
真正有可能的事情，这会让你达到……
the next level like I've brought a CEO
就像我请来一位
into represent that was handling a $500
管理着5亿美元企业的CEO代表我，
business that at the time it was only
当时我的公司年营业额只有
doing 20 mil and to tell me what's
2000万美元，他告诉我各种
possible and run me through different
可能性，并带我了解不同的
geographies and how products can have a
地域市场，以及产品如何拥有
lifetime and how you can maintain a
生命周期，如何让
constant like steady sale of one product
一款产品多年保持稳定的销量。而我们之前的
thinking that you put something online
想法只是把产品放到网上，
let it sell out and then you move on to
卖完就去做下一款。但实际上有
the next thing and there's so many
很多
different like factors that can come in
不同的因素会影响增长，
and different areas of growth and sales
不同的增长领域、销售渠道、产品类别等等，这些都会让
things that just make you realize oh you
你意识到，你
can turn the business from 20 to 50 mil
可以通过一些方法把公司从2000万美元发展到5000万美元。
this but you would never know that if
但如果
you were just in your little group of
你一直待在你那群从小一起
people that you've grown up with and
长大、一直合作的小圈子里，你永远不会知道这一点，
done it with forever and you don't even
你甚至不知道，
know that you don't know it like it's an
你不知道，你不知道，就像一个
unknown know no because there's no one
未知的未知领域，因为没有人
teaching you and I and that's why I'm
教你。这就是为什么我
trying to do this YouTube channel and
尝试做这个YouTube频道，
trying to be so expressive but also um
努力表达自己，同时也保持
like authentic on the YouTube and on
真诚。 在YouTube和
Instagram by telling people this and
Instagram上，我会告诉大家这些，并
showing them how what we actually do and
展示我们实际的运作方式。
how we do it because when I was 18
因为我18岁
starting this brand I had nowhere to
创立这个品牌的时候，根本无处可去，
look I had no mentors I there was no one
没有导师，
in fashion that would wanted to come and
时尚圈里也没有人愿意来
help us and there's nothing like that I
帮我们。
could just go online and find and and
网上根本找不到任何资源，
buying a course to build a brand isn't
买个课程来打造品牌根本
going to work that's that's the biggest
行不通，那纯粹是
load of [__] ever um so like you're
胡扯。所以，你会
stuck in your own in your own ways and
被困在自己的思维模式里，你的
beliefs and you don't know what you
认知很局限，你不知道自己
don't know so how you how again if you
不知道什么。所以，如果你
could like go back cuz there's so many
能回到过去，你会怎么做？因为有很多
young kids that are going to be looking
年轻人会仰慕
up to you thinking okay George I get it
你，他们会想：乔治，我明白了，有
there's lots of things that I don't know
很多事情我不知道，
where do I go to find the answers what's
我该去哪里寻找答案？怎样才能
the best way to go to find these answers
找到这些答案，
that are going to help me go to the next
帮助我更上一层楼？
level I think you got to research now I
我觉得你必须做研究。现在
think everyone's very explicitly
每个人在网上都非常注重
authentic online like if they want to be
真实性，比如，如果他们想成为
the next George Heaton you can scroll
下一个乔治·希顿，你可以往下翻。 你可以
and see exactly what I've done and where
看看我过去十年的Instagram，了解我做了什么，
I've been and how I've done it who we've
去过哪里，以及我是如何做到的，和谁一起完成的。
done it with or you can go on the
或者你也可以去我们的
YouTube channel and backload a
YouTube频道，下载
documentary that we did three years ago
我们三年前制作的纪录片，回顾
that shows the last 10 years and then
过去十年。
now you do it with um the diary of the
现在，我们还推出了
SE behind behind the scenes as well so
SE的幕后日记，所以
the people are willing as well to like
大家也都愿意
give you advice I give people advice on
给我建议。我经常在社交媒体上给别人提建议，
social media all the time but that
但是
decision then to bring in that
当初决定聘请那位
CEO where did that information come from
CEO，这些信息又是从哪里来的呢？
I spent a good couple years just really
我花了整整两年时间
like rebuilding myself when that when
重塑自我，当时公司发展遇到了瓶颈。大概有
18 months to two years where it was just
18个月到2年的时间，就在
before Co started and I wanted to just
公司成立之前，我渴望把
like really build myself up into someone
自己打造成一个与当时截然不同的人。
to be why what was going on in your
为什么
world I I felt like I was stuck and like
我感觉自己被困住了，就像
like I said we we had limited beliefs we
我之前说的，我们当时的信念很局限，
didn't know where to go and what to do
不知道该何去何从。
if I'm not got a mentor or someone
如果没有导师或任何人
telling me which way to go with it I've
指引，我该如何找到方向呢？ 我得
got to do it myself so it was like read
自己想办法，所以我就读了
every single self- health book look into
所有关于自我健康的书，看了
every single fashion show figure out
每一场时装秀，想弄清楚
like what it is we want to do and where
我们想做什么，
we want to go with this brand and how
这个品牌想发展到什么程度，以及
we're going to build it up but also with
我们该如何建立它，同时也要反思我们
ourselves was this the period in 2018
自己。
where you said you lost the motivation
你说的失去
for the business yeah just before that
对事业动力的时期是不是就是2018年？是的，就在那之前。请你描述一下
take me into that period of your life if
你人生中的那段时期。如果
I'm a if I'm a fly on the wall what do I
我是个旁观者，我能从
see in in your world at that time where
你的世界里看到什么？
you're like not excited about it not
你当时对事业提不
excited about it because we were getting
起劲，因为我们受到了
a lot of push back from press and like
很多媒体的抨击，
we were trying to do runway shows and
我们尝试举办时装秀，但
no stores wanted to buy us and our price
没有商店愿意进货，我们的定价
points weren't right and the way we were
不合理，
taking the design wasn't right and that
设计理念也不对。这很
was like painful because it was a
痛苦，因为这是
passion for us it was our love so like
我们的热情所在，是我们挚爱的事业。所以，那些
that negative feedback was like kind of
负面反馈
painful at the time but we used it as
在当时确实很伤人，但我们把它当作
like a reset button and I looked at
一个重启按钮。同时，我也反思了
myself as well at the same time and like
自己，意识到
I wasn't putting everything into the
我没有全身心投入到这个
brand I wasn't going like full on with
品牌中。 当时我并没有全力以赴，只是在
it I was messing around and like
瞎混，
enjoying in my life as well cuz we were
享受生活，因为
making money at that time like more than
那时我们赚的钱比
what we should have been doing in our
我们
early 20s so we're [__] around a lot
二十出头应该赚的要多得多，所以我们经常瞎混。我
and I'm not going to sit here and lie
不会坐在这里撒谎，我们当时根本
like we would we didn't know what we
不知道自己在
were doing we were messing around and it
做什么，只是瞎混，结果到了后来，
just got to a point where like that year
那一年公司开始
became unprofitable and for me to sit
亏损。我坐在那里想，操，我做了
for the past seven or eight years and
七八年了，
now it's not making money that was like
现在却赚不到钱，就是这件事彻底
was a car list that just changed
改变了
everything I just took a real good hard
一切。我认真地
look at what we are and who we were and
审视了我们，审视了我们是谁，然后彻底改变了。你
a personal level at that at that time
当时个人情况如何？
you said you weren't happy with yourself
你说你对自己不满意，
didn't why I hated the way I looked I
不知道为什么。我讨厌自己的外表，
hated the way I came across on social
讨厌自己在社交
media I was very shy very
媒体上的形象。我很害羞，很不
unconfident
自信，很不会
um like terrible at hiring people and
招人，而且总是很生气，不是说我有什么
just didn't like had not anger issues
情绪问题，
but was always angry was always negative
而是总是很生气。 我总是很消极，对
everything
什么都抱有悲观的看法，
even the weather had pissed me
就连天气都让我很生气，这种情况持续了很
off um for a for a long time and I just
长时间。我
remember reading a few books and
记得当时读了几本书，一直在
thinking like why am I this way and how
想我为什么会这样，
do I change myself I even and like being
我该如何改变自己。我甚至，作为一个
the artist I even redrew how I wanted to
艺术家，我重新画了我想要的样子。
think this this this is I wanted to
感觉就像我每天都要努力成为我想要的那个乔治·希顿，而不是现在的我。你真的画了一幅画，是的，是的，是的，是的。我以前经常翻看那幅画，想着这就是我想要
recreate myself and recreate the brand
重塑的自己，重塑我的品牌。
what was the base you were starting from
你当时的起点是什么？
at that point and how old were you at
你当时多大了？
this point 20 six I think I was 25 26 I
206？我想应该是25、26岁。我当时的
relationship with the way I worked and
工作方式，
even the food I at and like I wasn't I
甚至饮食习惯，都让我很不健康。我不健康，状态很差，
didn't look great like didn't didn't
看起来也不好，
feel myself I didn't want to look at
感觉不像自己，我都不想照
myself in the mirror um you didn't want
镜子。 是的，我不想
to look at yourself in the mirror yeah
照镜子，
because I didn't like who I'd become and
因为我不喜欢现在的自己，
like the I didn't like what the brand
也不喜欢品牌
had become either and the brand was my
变成现在的样子，而品牌就是我的
life so it was like this all needs to
生命。所以我觉得这一切都需要
change when you say you didn't want to
改变。你说你不想照
look at yourself in the mirror do you
镜子，你是
actually mean that or you saying that as
真的不想照镜子，还是只是个
like a figure of speech I guess a figure
比喻？我想是
of speech but as well like realizing
比喻吧，但也意识到自己
that that I wanted to change a lot so
想要改变很多。那么，当
then when when you do want to change
你真的想要改变，并且
then you don't like the way you are how
不喜欢现在的自己时，你怎么知道自己想要改变呢？对我来说，
me that sounds like an like a slightly
这听起来像个
peculiar question but I always think
有点奇怪的问题，但我一直在思考，
about what it takes for someone to have
一个人要经历怎样的阶段才会
they go you know what enough is enough
意识到“够了，真的够了”。是的，
yeah and sometimes I've always like
我有时会
pondered I think I've said it a few
思考，我想我
times on the show like do people have to
在节目里也说过几次，人们是否必须
reach a certain Rock Bottom in their
跌到人生的谷底才会彻底改变？
And I see this with people now that um
我现在看到有些人就是这样，比如
we Inspire with 247 or who will send me
我们“Inspire with 247”节目的嘉宾，或者其他什么人会给我发
a DM and say look you've changed my life
信息。 我会私信你，说你
through this or that the I think the
通过这个或那个改变了我的人生。我觉得就像“
like the best view of Heaven is from
天堂的最佳视角来自
hell right I think you've got to get to
地狱”这句话一样，对吧？我觉得你必须先到达
the bottom of that mountain to start re
山脚才能重新开始
climbing it I think if you just sit
攀登。如果你只是待在山腰，觉得
life's just is what it is that was what
人生就这样，那就太糟糕了。
I was going through um and like I had a
我当时就是这种状态。嗯，我有个
girlfriend and we'd split up and that
女朋友，我们分手了，那感觉
was terrible and yeah the brand wasn't
糟透了。而且，我的品牌也经营
doing well I got told it was
不善，有人告诉我它不盈利。
unprofitable and like I was just in this
我当时真的跌到了
[__] what for me was rock bottom and
谷底。
I know it doesn't sound bad compared to
我知道跟
a lot of other people's lives I
很多人的生活相比，这听起来不算什么，我
understand that but for me for where I'd
明白。但对我来说，就我当时的人生
been on the trajectory that I thought I
轨迹而言，这真的是
was on it was Rock Bottom so was that
谷底。所以，这就像是一次
was like the reset so you drew a picture
重启。你画了一幅
of yourself and how you wanted to look
自己想要的样子，有没有
did you write anything about who you
写下你
wanted to be in terms of values or yeah
想成为什么样的人，比如你的价值观？
I've got a best friend who's done a very
我有个好朋友也经历过
similar transformation and they
类似的转变，她
literally wrote down like a set of
真的写下了一套
principles and it's it's in the notes of
原则，就写在
their phone it's my friend Anthony and
她的笔记里。 手机是给我朋友安东尼的，
he went from being in a place in his
他之前的
life where he also figuratively couldn't
生活状态很糟糕，甚至不敢
look himself in the mirror dropped
照镜子。后来他戒了
alcohol hit the gym and has turned it
酒，开始健身，彻底改变了自己的人生。
around and he he has almost has this
他手机
like Ten Commandments in the notes of
备忘录里几乎写着“十诫”。
his phone yeah you did something similar
是啊，你也做过类似的事情，
exactly the same and still have them
而且我手机里也一直保留着这些“十诫”，
that pop up every morning like reminders
每天早上都会弹出提醒。
on my phone um I found this guy called
我认识一个叫
Andy fitell and he had a book
安迪·菲特尔的人，他写了一本书
called um 75 hard and it was like a
叫《75天挑战》，这本书是一个
mental toughness challenge but it also
精神韧性挑战，
included a lot of working out in there
里面也包含了很多健身内容。
and it was like no alcohol drink this
比如，每天不喝酒，喝一定量的
much water read this much of a book and
水，读一定数量的书，连续
just do it every single day for 75 days
75天，每天
write down five things you're going to
写下五件
do that day and I did that and I started
当天要做的事情。我照做了，开始
doing it and I started seeing like these
执行，然后我的
crazy results in my life just with
生活发生了翻天覆地的变化。一切都变得不一样了，
everything just the way I could
我能更好地
structure my day and knowing that like I
安排自己的时间。比如，我知道自己一天
had to put two workouts into a day one
必须进行两次锻炼，一次
had to be outside wanted to be inside so
必须在户外，一次必须在室内，然后围绕这些锻炼来
structure the rest of the day around
安排剩下的时间。
that and then started learning how to
之后，我开始学习如何
plan my day out better and where the
更好地规划一天，以及如何安排
time was where I could go and do these
时间。 那是我可以去的地方，可以做
other things and like every night I
其他事情。比如，我每天晚上
would read 10 pages of a book whichever
都会读十页书，不管是什么
book that was
书，
from all the ran holiday books and
从Ran Holiday系列到
Robert Green and everything like that so
罗伯特·格林的作品，等等。
I was learning all these things whilst I
我一边学习这些东西，一边
was also doing this mental toughness
进行着这个为期
Challenge and it was like a 75 day thing
75天的心理韧性挑战。
and I remember getting to getting to the
我记得快到挑战
end of it and just thinking [__] like
结束的时候，我心想：妈的，我到底是怎么做到的？
I'm I looked at myself then and I was
我看着自己，心想：
like okay I can see the change and you
好吧，我看到了变化。你
know when you can see change that's when
知道，当
you like really go into it you start
你看到变化的时候，你就会真正投入进去，开始
getting obsessed when you see whether
痴迷。你会看到无论
it's success or like your Fitness levels
是成功，还是体能的提升，
go up or just the way you energy levels
或是每天精力水平的变化，你都会
are every day and just figuring out that
意识到
like these little indicators are
这些小小的指标正在
changing the way I'm and then at the
改变着我。与此同时，
same time we were really working on the
我们也在努力发展
business so the business was starting to
业务，业务开始取得
see a bit more success and that whole
一些进展。这一切就这样持续不断地进行着。
rolling and rolling and rolling and I
我
guess whether it's Obsession or
想，不管是痴迷还是
addiction I got addicted to it and like
上瘾，我都对它上瘾了。我
there couldn't be a day go by where I
每天都必须
wouldn't work out or I wouldn't eat the
工作。 否则我就吃不下
exact calories that I needed to eat or I
我需要的卡路里，也
wouldn't sleep the exact like and I
睡不着我
needed to get the exact amount of sleep
需要的睡眠时间，
that I wanted and it just completely
这彻底
changed like the way I looked and the
改变了我的外貌，我的体能、
cardiovascular and strength and
心肺功能、力量等等都突飞猛进，
the roof cuz people will look at you now
因为人们现在看到我，会
and think that you know they'll see you
觉得我早上
getting up at I don't know 5:00 a.m. in
五点就起床，跑个
the morning and going for like a 20 mile
20英里，晚上再去
run um and hit in the gym later that
健身房，同时还要经营生意，做这么多
these things being super productive and
事情，效率超高。他们可能会
they'll probably think he was just born
觉得我天生就拥有
with something that I don't have right
我没有的特质，
like he's just got this level of
比如我天生就拥有这种动力，而这种
motivation probably came in his DNA that
动力可能来自我的基因。
say that a lot of people think that
很多人都这么说，他们觉得这是
think it's genetics or they think it's
基因决定的，或者用了类
steroids and stuff like that or they'll
固醇之类的，或者觉得我
way from birth I used to think that as
天生就具备这种能力。以前
well back when I was overweight and
我超重的时候也这么想。
unhealthy and like I'd look at people on
不健康，就像我以前在Instagram上看别人身材好的时候，会想：是啊，
Instagram be like yep genetics whatever
基因什么的，是啊，
yep he's on steroids I can't look like
他肯定用了类固醇，我可没法练成那样，
that I've got a business to run like you
我还要经营生意呢。就像你一样，你会对
would you dismiss everything but it's
一切都不屑一顾，但事实并非如此。
not and once you start doing it yourself
一旦你开始自己实践，
and you see those little gains and you
看到那些小小的进步，当你
you get into it you you can really
真正投入其中，你就能
change what is the starting point one
改变现状。起点就是一步一步，
step at a time whether it's 10,000 steps
不管是走一万步，
or doing even a 20 minute workout that's
还是做个20分钟的锻炼，这都是
all people need to do to
人们
change because you'll start seeing
改变所需要的全部。因为
results regardless of what position
无论
you're in right now if you can just keep
你现在处于什么状态，只要你不断
increasing incrementally what you're
循序渐进地增加你
doing in terms of Fitness or your
在健身、
business or however like your sleep
事业、睡眠或其他任何
whatever it is that you feel is not
你觉得不合适的方面所做的事情，
right you'll see the change over time it
你就会开始看到效果。改变终会
comes and it takes a long time takes a
到来，这需要很长时间，真的非常
really long time but it it happens it's
长，但它终究会发生。
guess for some people because they they
有些人可能很难相信，因为他们眼前仿佛有一
kind of they see the mountain in front
座大山，
of them and you're telling them listen
而你却告诉他们，听着，你
it's just one step at a time up that
只需要一步一步地爬上这座
mountain but they're just looking at the
山。 但他们只是望着山顶，
that's a long way away and the thought
心想“我的天哪，那还远着呢”，而想到
that the the first steps to take are
第一步其实是
small ones doesn't almost doesn't seem
小步前进，这几乎让人难以置信。
believable yeah and and look same with
是啊，你看，我也一样，我以前会一头扎进
something thinking that you could just
某件事里，以为
go out there and run a marathon within a
一周就能跑完马拉松，有些
week and people do that and it and it it
人确实这么做了，结果却被彻底
crushes you and and then you have to
击垮，然后不得不重新
start again but it's just about finding
开始。关键在于找到
the rhythm of like what you enjoy and
自己喜欢的节奏，
and just going and just doing it and not
然后坚持下去，
once you start doing it so jumping back
一旦开始就不要松懈。回到
to 2018 then so the business is stagnant
2018年，那段时间公司业务停滞不前，你开始了自我重塑的过程，
this process of Reinventing yourself um
嗯，
you also go on the process of
你也开始了业务重塑的过程。是的，这是
Reinventing the business yeah what does
什么
that mean how did you reinvent the
意思？你是如何重塑业务的？
business we stripped back all the
我们剥离了所有批发业务，
focused on the DTC so we went into this
专注于DTC（直接面向消费者），所以我们开始
weekly drop thing and it was just right
每周发布新品，这正合时宜，就在新
it was just before like covid happened
冠疫情爆发之前。
and James who is the chief product
詹姆斯是首席执行官。 产品
officer was like super keen on moving
经理当时特别热衷于把
our production out to Portugal it was
生产线搬到葡萄牙，它
currently in the UK and Italy and it was
当时在英国和意大利，而且根本
making no money and I had so many
不赚钱。我为此
arguments with him about it and like
跟他争论了很多次，我非常
hated this this way of thinking that he
讨厌他的这种想法，以及
was doing and like what he wanted to do
他
with the business and it got to like we
对公司未来的规划。
we had a massive heated argument about
我们为此爆发了一场激烈的争吵。但当时这
it and it was so right for the business
对公司来说确实是正确的，只是
at the time and I just didn't know it
我当时不理解，
cuz I weren't acceptance AC accepting of
因为我无法接受
like changing changing the way we were
改变。 我们之前的
working and I didn't understand that you
工作方式，我当时并不理解，原来你
could go and do this other thing
可以去做其他事情，用和我们完全
and produce in a different way than what
不同的方式进行生产。我必须
we were doing and like full credit to
承认，
him he completely changed the whole like
他彻底改变了我们整个工作的
margin of what we were doing um so James
格局。詹姆斯
straight and Mike was doing all these
连续九个月都在做这件事，迈克则设计了一系列
new graphics that was going to change
全新的图案，旨在改变
the way the brand looked and then I I
品牌的形象。之后我
came out to LA a few times and Bone
去了几次洛杉矶，买了几件
these t-shirts that I really loved and
我非常喜欢的T恤和
these cargo pants that I loved and then
工装裤。然后
we started putting all these three
我们开始把这三样
things together through through all of
东西整合起来，我们所有人一起努力。
us and then I have a guy called Stefan
我还有一个叫斯特凡的人
who was doing all the Website
负责网站
Maintenance and everything like that and
维护等等，
we changed the way the website looked
我们改变了网站的风格，也改变了
and the whole vision of the brand and we
整个品牌的愿景。我们
deleted everything off social media and
删除了所有社交媒体账号，一切重新开始。结果真的奏效了！
started working and we put like 300
我们上架了300件
t-shirts online and we sold 300 in a
T恤，一
minute and then the next week Mike did
分钟就卖光了。接下来的一周，迈克又
another design and we sold 600 in a
设计了一款T恤，一
minute and then 900 in a minute and then
分钟就卖出了600件，然后是900件。我们当时
it was like [__] we actually do have a
就想：卧槽，我们真的有
following here we've gone from
粉丝了！我们成功了！ 从
doing 10 15 sales through the day to
每天只能卖出10到15件，到
like a thousand every single Wednesday
每周三都能卖出1000件，甚至
4,000 and that gave us like the the
2000、3000、4000件，这给了我们
liquid and also the confidence to then
资金和信心，让我们能够继续
go and create more Collections and go
开发更多系列，
back to becoming a real brand again as
重新打造一个真正的品牌。正如
you were saying that made me think about
你所说，这让我想到
how so many people aren't successful in
很多人在生活中并不成功，
their lives or aren't as successful as
或者没有发挥出
they could possibly be
他们应有的潜力，
because they haven't gotten out of their
因为他们没有克服
own way and that was me a million times
自身的障碍。我以前就是这样，而且不止一次。
over and just like having that open
保持开放的
mindedness and listening to other people
心态，倾听他人的意见，
and knowing that it's not you're not
并且明白并非所有事情都是你对的，
huge thing it's difficult when you I
这真的非常重要。我
think especially if you're a young CEO
觉得这对年轻的CEO来说尤其困难，
because you're probably already a bit
因为你可能本身就有点不
insecure right yeah 100% yeah um like
自信，对吧？没错，百分之百是这样。
you feel like you should know everything
你会觉得自己应该什么都懂，
so you're like overcompensating by but
所以你会过度补偿。但
then as well like the business was
同时，业务
growing so much that I would have only
发展如此迅速，
just restricted it if I would have
如果我
stayed in that CEO position even though
继续担任CEO，即使
I was learning a lot and listening a lot
我学到了很多，也听取了很多意见，最终也只会限制业务的发展。
to a lot of things and we had to bring
很多事情，我们不得不招
people in because we were like busting
人，因为公司
at the seams didn't have enough staff
人手严重不足，简直要爆棚了。
and like the revenue was going crazy and
营收却一路飙升，
we didn't know what to do with ourselves
我们都不知道该怎么办，像
we're all running around like headless
无头
chicken there's only like 20 people in
苍蝇一样乱窜。公司只有20个人，营收却达到了
the business and we were doing like 30
3000万到
35 million revenue and it was like [__]
3500万美元，当时我们就想：完了，
how what are we going to do we're going
我们该怎么办？
to do 50 million next year but we we
明年营收要达到5000万美元，但我们却完全
don't know what we're doing just like so
不知道该怎么做，真是太
silly but yeah
傻了。不过，
you I'm going to say from the outside it
从表面上看，
looks like you you had it all together
你们似乎一切都井井有条，
of course it does yeah for the whole 13
当然是这样。过去13
years it kind of looks like that um and
年里，看起来确实如此，
it still looks like that now and we
现在也依然如此。我们
definitely don't have it all together
当然没有完全掌控一切，
but we I do have an amazing like
但我确实拥有一支非常优秀的
leadership team and everyone in the
领导团队，公司里的每个人都全身心投入其中。
business is like so bought into it now
现在我们有了
and like now there's like a mission
使命
statement and some fundamentals behind
宣言，有了公司的基本原则，每个人都和
really on the mission with me and like
我一样，真正地朝着这个目标努力，
they they [__] live for it and love
他们为之奋斗，热爱它。
it and like we die for it you've you've
你为之奋斗终生，你
created a pretty amazing um company
创造了一种非常棒的公司
culture you were talking about it there
文化，你刚才也谈到了。是的，
yeah how have you done that that's it's
你是怎么做到的？其实
not really I'm not going to sit here and
我不会坐在这里
take credit for that um I'll take credit
邀功，嗯，我会为
for like the gym that we have in there
我们公司里的健身房
and and the way we like everyone works
以及我们鼓励每个人努力工作的方式感到自豪。还有，就像我们新
hard but also like my the CEO that came
来的CEO
in Spenny just he's all about people
Spenny一样，他非常重视人，
people over a profit every day of the
人比利润更重要，每天都是如此，
week whatever it is it's people first so
无论做什么，都是以人为本。所以
we have such a good like group of
我们拥有一个非常优秀的
like the leadership theme he's brought
领导团队，他带来了这种理念，
the business now it's just constant like
现在所有参与公司运营的人都保持着高度的
transparency and here's where we go
透明度，他会告诉员工我们的发展方向、正在做的事情、哪里出了问题、
wrong here's what's right we need to
哪里做得对，我们需要
focus more on this we need to do more of
更加关注这一点，我们需要在这一点上做得更多，
this and just giving them everything
并且尽力满足
that they they want and like even though
他们的需求。虽然，是的，
it's yeah you got to work hard you got
你必须努力工作，你必须非常努力，但
to work [__] hard we're still like
我们仍然可能是
for that I know of self-awareness I amum
我所知的最好的工作场所，因为员工的自我认知能力很强。
I've spoken to a lot of Founders that
我跟很多非常成功的创始人聊过，
especially out of Europe and one of the
尤其是欧洲的创始人。
things that they all seem to have in
他们似乎都有一个
common is at some point in their Journey
共同点：在创业的某个阶段，
they developed such a high
他们都培养了高度的
self-awareness that as we kind of said
自我认知。​​正如我们刚才提到的，
they got out of the way of the business
他们不再干预业务，
and just focused on the thing that
而是专注于自己擅长的领域。这
at and that's pretty much what it looks
看起来也正是
like you're doing now yeah and I hope
你现在正在做的。是的，我希望我的理解没错。
that's right and I've seen people do
我见过有人这样做，但最终却
that and get it wrong but for me I think
失败了。不过对我来说，我认为你的做法
it is right I'm not a businessman and
是正确的。我不是商人，如果
like for me to be the CEO of this
我担任这家
business it's growing rapidly and has
快速发展、
all these people involved with it like
人员众多的公司的CEO，我只会
all I would do is stump the growth of it
阻碍它的发展。
um so like you said earlier today like
就像你今天早些时候说的，
there's people that are so much better
有些人比
at things than you and if you can bring
你更擅长某些事情。如果你能把
them into your business they can they
他们招进你的公司，他们
can get on with that stuff and do 10
就能把事情做好，而且做得
times better job than you can and lay
比你好十倍，
the foundations for it to become 500
为公司发展成为五亿美元、
million or a billion dollar brand or 10
十亿美元甚至
billion dollar brand and you can focus
百亿美元的品牌奠定基础。这样你就可以专注
on what you're actually good at how did
于真正重要的事情了。 你真的很擅长如何
you get them to come I think like you
吸引他们加入。我觉得就像你
said then like company culture like
说的，公司文化很重要。
you see if you see represent on LinkedIn
如果你在LinkedIn或其他平台上看到他们的形象，
or something you're going to look at it
你肯定会想：
and think [__] I want to be in there
天哪，我也想加入！
these guys and girls are getting after
这些男男女女工作都很拼，早上
6:00 a.m. and they're all out and they
六点就一起去健身房，而且他们都很
just they're just enjoying the workplace
享受工作环境。
like but that that comes from being
但这都源于
being a successful brand you can't just
打造一个成功的品牌，你不可能一开始就
do that from the get-go can't just build
做到这一点，你不可能
a gym with no money right so you've got
没钱就建一个健身房，对吧？所以你必须先
to build that level of success and then
建立起那种程度的成功，然后才能把资金
you're able to reinvest into the brand
再投资到品牌建设上，
rather than into your stock and and
而不是投资股票，并
building the actual size of the company
扩大公司的实际规模。
because this is always the issue that I
因为我总是
hear specifically like young Founders or
听到年轻的创始人或
early stage entrepreneurs talking about
早期创业者谈论这个问题：“
is okay Steve I get it I know we need
史蒂夫，我明白，我知道我们需要
great people but how do I persuade great
优秀的人才，但我该如何说服像
people like Spencer it's Spenny right
斯宾塞这样的人才呢？是斯宾塞，对，
Paul Spencer yeah Paul Spencer um how do
保罗·斯宾塞，嗯，
I get him to come work here right when
我该如何让他来这里工作呢？
he's working at like Puma he was at Puma
他之前在彪马工作。” 彪马？
wasn't he yeah he was you get how did
他不是吗？是的，他就是。你明白
you get him to come from Puma to
你是怎么让他从彪马过来
represent built a relationship with him
代言的吗？我们和他建立了
over many years James was in contact
多年的关系。詹姆斯
with him for 5 years since we first met
从我们第一次见面起就和他保持联系，持续了五年。随着
and then as the business scaled he saw
业务规模的扩大，他
what we had like he saw what me and Mike
看到了我们拥有的东西，看到了我和迈克像
had together as brothers and he saw what
兄弟一样的情谊，也看到了
me Mike James and Steph had as like a
我、迈克、詹姆斯和斯蒂芬组成的
leadership team and he wanted to be
领导团队，他想
involved with it because he knows that
参与其中，因为他知道
there's no other options for us it was
我们别无选择。
like we we're building this there's no
就像我们正在打造一个没有上限的品牌，
representing 10 years like what can it
代表着十年，它能做到什么？
be and he says it every day is like
他每天都这么说，每次
gives me [__] Goosebumps walking in
走进这里我都激动得起鸡皮疙瘩，
here because there's no there's no limit
因为没有极限，我们
to it like can do everything if we can
可以做任何事。如果我们能
spell sell sportsware we can sell
拼写出“sell sportswear”，我们就能卖
vintage t-shirts and we can
复古T恤，我们甚至
sell we can sell salt like it's insane
能卖盐，简直不可思议，
we can do anything it's it's not really
我们什么都能做。这已经不再是
a brand anymore it's like a lifestyle of
一个品牌了，它更像是一种生活方式，是
all the business decisions that you've
你所有商业决策的体现。
made where does hiring a CEO to run the
聘请CEO来运营
business and you stepping out of the way
公司，然后你退出，这又有什么意义呢？
rank number one really
排名第一的方式真的
yeah my life's just so much better now
太棒了，自从
that he's involved with the business and
他参与公司运营后，我的生活真的好多了，肩上的担子也轻了
there's a lot of way taken off my
很多。
shoulders it's not the first time I've
这也不是我第一次
heard this I think Ben Francis would
听到这种说法了，我想本·弗朗西斯也会这么
have said the same yeah I bet you know
说。没错，我敢肯定，
in julan at hu said the same and that
朱兰和胡也说过同样的话。让
putting someone in in that CEO role
一个既不
where it's both like not enjoyable for
享受
you as a creative but also it's not good
创意工作，又对
for the business because it's not your
公司不利的人来担任CEO，因为那不是你的
skill set and and that yeah it wasn't
专长。是的，很长一段时间以来，这都不是件
enjoyable for a for a long time and you
愉快​​的事，你
do it because you had to do it and if I
做这件事只是因为不得不做。如果我
spent 6 hours in that role of a CEO to
花了6个小时担任CEO，
then come out of my room and be like
然后走出房间说：“
Mike let's go and Design This thing you
迈克，我们去设计这个东西吧。”你根本
didn't want to do it there's no energy
不想做，那会
that [__] drains your if you're a
耗尽你的精力。如果你是
creative the business side of the thing
创意人员，公司运营方面的事情会
drains your energy it absolutely kills
耗尽你的精力，简直要了
you even to this day I'll go into a
你的命。即使到了今天，我参加
board meeting and after 15 minutes I'm
董事会，15分钟后我就会
just like oh my God I'm I'm done I'm
想：“我的天哪，我受够了。” 我
asleep but I could sit in Mike's room
睡着了，但我可以坐在Mike的房间里和
him how much as a creative and a
他一起设计12个小时。作为一名创意人士和
creative founder do you have to stay in
创意创始人，你到底需要
touch with the business side of things
对商业方面保持多少联系？
though like you spoke about the
就像你刚才提到的
boardroom do you still kind of need to
董事会，你还需要
know what's going on I like to yeah okay
了解正在发生的事情吗？是的，
I I love to know as much as I can um but
我喜欢尽可能多地了解。但是，
as well I think you should keep things
我认为你也应该让
away from yourself because it will
自己远离一些事情，因为
inflict you with even if it's like
即使是
negative things I think especially if
负面的事情，也会对你产生影响。特别是当
you're so focused on building this next
你专注于打造下一个
collection or whatever it is if you're
系列或其他项目时，如果你
hearing negative feedback about some
听到一些关于某个
kind of product that's not working or
产品或
something in the business is not working
业务中某些环节出现问题的负面反馈，
that affects what you're doing there um
这会影响你的工作。所以，
so I think trying to divide them two
我认为将这两者分开
things is crucial and I did that with
至关重要。我
Mike from the GetGo cuz I knew that like
从一开始就和Mike这样做，因为我知道，
negativity and um like feedback loops on
负面情绪和关于不好的事情的反馈循环对
for him when he's designing so kind of
他的设计工作不利，所以我让他
kept him just like strictly to design
专注于设计，当然，
but obviously we'd give him facts and
我们也会给他提供事实、
figures and numbers and stuff like that
数据和诸如此类的信息。
but try and keep him out of it as much
尽量让他置身事外。
as he can what was your hardest
你最难熬的一天是什么时候？
day oh um I remember we got a letter
哦，嗯，我记得我们收到了一封来自欧洲一家
from a company also called represent in
也叫Represent的公司的信，信里
Europe telling us
说
that we we were basically
我们基本上
done and yeah that was that was the
完蛋了。是啊，那是我们生意上最
worst day in the business yeah what did
糟糕的一天。
the L say just said like that they owned
信里说了什么？就说他们拥有我们
the trademark in Europe
在欧洲的商标权，
were they were just going to take us for
他们要把我们所有的钱都榨干，
everything we had we couldn't carry on
我们没法继续做下去了。
they wanted all of your money more than
他们想要的钱比
what we
我们
had and that that like that was in that
拥有的还多。那段
same period that 2018 to 20 where we
时间，也就是2018到2020年，
were just like every day we were waiting
我们每天都在等
for responses and every day it was like
回复。每天醒来都
waking up and thinking [__] like is it
想着：完了，
all over today is it all over tomorrow
今天是不是结束了？明天是不是也结束了？
can we do what we want to do is this
我们还能做我们想做的事吗？这
even our business anymore do we even own
还是我们的生意吗？我们还拥有
what we're doing and like there was
我们做的一切吗？当时
there was only really me Mike and James
只有我和Mike还有James
that knew about this that was going on
知道这件事，
cuz I didn't want to put it out to
因为我不想让任何人知道，不想让
business to know like this was happening
业内人士知道，甚至不想让
or even my family um and it really
我的家人知道。这件事真的
[__] like restricted us with
限制了我们的
everything we did every decision we made
一切。 我们做的每一个决定，
every garment we
我们卖出的每一件衣服，都包含
included in that really dark period they
在那段非常黑暗的时期里。他们
presumably owned the trademark that you
可能拥有你当时
were using so you had called yourself
使用的商标，所以你当时自称是
represent
Represent，
but someone else owned the trademark for
但欧洲的商标权却属于别人。是的，
Europe yeah and you didn't realize that
你当时并没有意识到这一点，
at the time we thought we owned it um
我们以为我们拥有它，
because we had the UK IP and all over
因为我们拥有英国的知识产权，以及
the rest of the world and there was this
世界其他地区的知识产权。当时有一个
dormant we thought it was dormant but
休眠的商标，我们以为它处于休眠状态，但
apparently was selling clothing section
显然它属于第
25 or whatever section 25 is like the
25条（或者其他什么条款）的服装销售类别，第25条是
clothing category of a trademark right
商标权中关于服装的类别。
and at first we thought all right we can
起初我们想，好吧，我们
we'll we'll be able to figure this out
可以解决这个问题，我们
let's get some lawyers and we'll go into
找几个律师，
it in a certain way and approach it like
用某种特定的方式去处理，然后这样处理。但
no like they weren't willing to nothing
他们总是拒绝，什么都不愿意做。
and that was like that was the devil
这就像一个魔鬼，
that W you up every
每晚都折磨着你。
night um but I used that as like I guess
但我把它当作一种
again it's that chip on the shoulder
耿耿于怀的东西，
thing I kind of used it as that and I
我把它当作一种动力，我
realized that like we had to get we had
意识到我们必须
to do so much and make so much of the
做很多事情，必须让
brand that we didn't want to give it up
品牌发展壮大。 他不想放弃，
and that when it when the time came to
但到了最后关头，
it and he gave in and he wanted to take
他还是妥协了，想要拿走我们的
money we had the money to be able to do
钱。我们当时也有足够的钱。2018
it this sort of dark period between 2018
年
and sort of 2020 was did that cause it
到 2020 年这段黑暗时期是导致他妥协的原因吗？
or was that just on top of it that was
还是说这只是雪上加霜？
right so the business is stagnant and
生意停滞不前，
then you get this letter through someone
然后你收到一封信，说有人
wants to take everything you have and we
想拿走你的一切。我们
spent so many months like just sat in
花了几个月的时间，就坐在
the back office just figuring out what
办公室里，琢磨着该如何
we're going to recall the brand how
召回这个品牌，如何
we're going to Rebrand it and like what
重新打造品牌，以及
it meant if it was not represent anymore
如果不再代表这个品牌会意味着什么。
and we wouldn't we couldn't post
我们不能
anything on social media so it was like
在社交媒体上发布任何内容，因为
we can't show this guy that the brand
我们不能向他展示品牌运营
does well or we're making any money
良好或盈利，否则
because then he'll want more and he'll
他会想要更多，他会
start seeing all these other things and
开始关注其他方面。我们当时完全被这件事困扰，
lawyers was just just always bad
律师给出的建议也总是坏
news um but eventually we got him to
消息。但最终，我们还是让他妥协了。
come up come up with a figure that he
他
wanted for it
要价很高，
and I remember it was I think it was
我记得好像是
March 2020 we ended up like signing and
2020年3月，我们最后签了约，
getting getting our name back he wanted
拿回了我们的名字。他想要
Millions
几百万，
yeah um you said the lawyers were giving
嗯，你说律师给了
you bad news what were they saying just
你坏消息，他们说了什么？比如他们
like they wouldn't respond for three
三个月都不回复。
months the lawyers no no no not the
律师？不不不，不是
lawyers his lawyers okay his lawyers
律师，是他的律师。好吧，他的律师。
okay so he and then they respond on the
然后他们在
last day of like this three Monon period
三个月期限的最后一天回复了，
but you'd be in the car going to like
但你当时正开车去
Portugal to find out if this
葡萄牙，想看看这个
production's ready and you'd get this
项目是否准备就绪，结果收到一封很
long email and your heart just drop and
长的邮件，你的心一下子沉了下去，
he'd be like what's going to get said
他会想接下来会说什么。
and then we' go back to the office and
然后我们回到办公室，又得
sit there again and try and rethink of
坐在那里，重新想一个
another name and then respond to him
名字，几天后再回复他，
within a few days and then be another
然后又是
three months so there was just this like
三个月。所以就像
this dark cloud above our heads all the
头顶一直笼罩着一片乌云。
time when you say Dark Cloud what does
你说“乌云”，那“
the Dark Cloud feel
乌云”是什么感觉？就像
like fly on the wall again yeah just you
墙上的苍蝇一样。是的，就是你
not being able to be yourself with
无法做自己，
everything you do every decision you
你做的每一件事，你做的每一个决定，
make whether it's buying a [__]
哪怕只是在
sandwich from the shop it's like that's
商店买个三明治。 感觉就像那
not your money to buy that sandwich cuz
不是你自己的钱去买三明治，因为
someone else owns a name where you're
别人拥有那个品牌，而你却在
making that that
用它赚钱。
money it' like get you like
这让你感觉很不好，
that did it interfere with your sleep
它影响了你的睡眠、
your mental health everything um but Al
心理健康等等。嗯，
but like I said earlier it also became
就像我之前说的，它也成了一种动力，我把
this driving force where like i' use it
它当成一种动力，就像
as a thing where it was like I know this
我知道这
Probably sounds so stupid but like I
听起来可能很傻，但我
just got started running in 2020 and I
2020年才开始跑步，我就想，
was like I'm going to go out and run 15K
我要去跑15公里，
and if I stop that's like him coming for
如果我停下来，就好像他会来找
us you know he's like I have to do it I
我们算账一样。你知道，他会说，我必须做到，我
have to win at everything we do whether
必须在我们做的每一件事上都赢，不管
it's just a run or it's a design selling
是跑步、设计销售
or whatever it is like you cannot stop
还是其他什么，你现在不能停下来。
with your brother as well because you're
和你的兄弟一起经历这些肯定不容易，因为
each other I imagine and if there's that
我想你们都会互相保护。如果
dark cloud hanging over both of you at
你们俩同时被这种阴云笼罩，那它就
the same time it's yeah it ruined both
毁了
of us it ruined his the way he designed
我们俩，毁了他的设计，毁了他的
and yeah everything and then So
一切。然后，
eventually you get a break and this guy
最终你得到了喘息的机会，这个人也
agrees to a
同意了……
figure and at the time I you know
当时，你知道，那可是几百万
millions and millions of pounds if
英镑啊！如果
you're making six or seven million in
你在公司赚了六七百万英镑，
the business and you're saying it's not
却说公司不怎么
really profitable I'm guessing the money
赚钱，我猜你
wasn't in the bank to send this guy
银行里肯定没钱给那家伙汇几
millions of pounds no but the deal went
百万英镑。不，但那笔交易
through in 2020 when we were really like
在2020年完成了，当时我们真的在全力
pushing forward and doing everything we
推进，竭尽所能。结果
could to that when that thing happened
那件事发生的时候，
we had enough money for it how do you
我们资金充足。你
feel about him this guy that sent you
对那个给你汇款的人有什么感觉？在那之前，我一直恨他，恨到骨子里
then just hate just absolute hate
恨他，
because
因为
we were a bunch of young guys that were
我们当时是一群年轻人，正
trying to build this business and we had
努力打造这家公司，我们有
20 employees at the time that we'd
20个员工，如果交易失败，
probably have to lay off and we'd lose
我们可能不得不解雇他们，
all the money and we'd be in debt for
我们会赔光所有钱，一辈子背债，就
because he decided that he wanted to use
因为他想用
that name to sell nothing basically
这个名字卖东西，实际上什么
wasn't selling anything
都没卖。
um so yeah up until that day I was I was
嗯，是的，在那之前，我一直很
really upset about it
生气。
but after it I kind of just realized
但之后，我意识到
things go and
事情就是这样，这就是人生。
and when I look back at it now it really
现在回想起来，这件事真的让我
[__] catapulted the business cuz
大吃一惊。 因为正是在那时，
that's when we came out of our shell and
我们走出了舒适圈，
that's when we started really like
开始真正把
building this brand into a lifestyle and
这个品牌打造成一种生活方式，而
not just t-shirts on the floor on an
不仅仅是在
Instagram page did your parents know
Instagram页面上卖T恤。你的父母知道
yeah that you were going through that
你当时的处境吗？是的，知道
yeah a little bit how I wouldn't tell
一点。但我不会告诉
them the full extent but why just cuz I
他们全部情况。为什么呢？因为
didn't I don't like putting pressure on
我不想给别人施加压力，
other people um especially when it's not
尤其是在当时这件事不会对
going to affect their lives as such at
他们的生活造成太大影响的情况下。我们
dad's every weekend and like it would
每个周末都会去我父母家，这
always be a subject that came up has he
总是一个会被提及的话题。他有
replied yet has he responded like have
回应吗？他有回应过吗？比如，
you heard anything it's just
你听说过什么吗？就好像，是的，这件事彻底
like yeah it [__] us how how did you
毁了我们。
how did you deal with that cuz you're a
你是怎么应对的？因为你还
young you're a young guy I remember the
年轻，你是个年轻人。我记得我
first time in business where I
第一次在工作中
experienced anxiety um I I thought
感到焦虑。我当时以为
anxiety was something that happens to
焦虑是
other people yeah and then I remember
别人才会有的事。然后我
the day very clearly where I had to let
清楚地记得，我不得不解雇
the managing director in our New York
纽约
office go I had to fire him right and I
办公室的总经理，我不得不解雇他。当时我
was sat in my apartment in Manchester
坐在曼彻斯特的公寓里，
thinking about that flight tomorrow
想着明天的航班。
where I I'd asked this person to come
我约了这个人来喝
coffee and I was just like riddled with
咖啡，结果我生平
anxiety for the first time ever I was
第一次感到焦虑不堪。我当时
like this is this is what people talk
想，这就是人们
about when they're talking about mental
谈论心理
health this is it it's happening to me I
健康时说的那种感觉吗？就是它，它发生在我身上了。我以前可是
Invincible but it's it's suddenly
所向披靡的，但它突然就发生在
happening happening to me um obviously
我身上了。嗯，当然，
as it always goes it was never it wasn't
就像往常一样，情况并没有
as bad as I imagined but it's the imag
我想象的那么糟糕，但
that imagination is 95% of it isn't it
想象占了95%，不是吗？
have you experienced that before um
你以前有过这种经历吗？嗯，
health I always struggle when people ask
当别人问我心理健康问题时，我总是很纠结，
me about this cuz no not really um I've
因为……不，我以前没有过。我一直
always been pretty solid on where I want
很清楚自己
to go who I want to be what I want to do
想去哪里，想成为什么样的人，想做什么事，
and just stuck to a plan um anxiety that
并且一直坚持计划。嗯，焦虑，就是
that thing that period yeah that caused
那段时间，是的，它让
me anxiety but not not to an extent
我焦虑，但并没有到那种让人
where it was like crippling mhm um but
崩溃的程度。嗯，
like I kind of now I kind of enjoy the
我现在有点享受这种
the bits of anxiety I get because you
焦虑的感觉，因为你可以
learn from it right like you going into
从中学习，对吧？比如你去
that meeting and telling him you're
开会，告诉他你开完会要被
going to get fired once that's done you
炒鱿鱼了，然后……
have that relief and then you know next
有了这种解脱感，下次再做的时候你就知道该
time you do it this is how it goes so
怎么做了，这样
you lose that 95% of anxiety that
你就能消除之前95%的焦虑，
happens before it or you lose a little
或者至少能消除
bit of it yeah I get really anxious
一部分。是的，我上
going on to podcasts like the past few
播客的时候真的很焦虑，就像过去
days I've been really anxious coming on
几天一样，我来这里录播客的时候也很焦虑，
here um and I've done a hundred of them
嗯，虽然我
before um so you never lose it but
之前已经录过上百次了，嗯，所以你永远不会完全失去这种焦虑。但
how'd you goope with it just being
你是怎么克服的呢？就是
prepared as much as you can for whatever
尽可能地为任何
that thing is so whe if that is you
事情做好准备。比如，如果你要
going to fire someone you got to know
解雇某人，你必须知道
the reasons why you're firing them like
解雇他们的理由，比如
where they can go what's going to be
他们可以去哪里，什么对他们
best for them what's going to be best
最好，什么
for you and just going into it like that
对你最好，就这样去处理。
um and then there's nothing really that
嗯，这样一来，
can happen within that meeting then that
会议中就不会发生什么意外了，
that can go wrong I think and I think
我认为
that kind of clears the
这能消除
anxiety on your on the brands you know
你对品牌的焦虑。你知道，
you've gone through a bit of a
你经历了一段
transition you said you was the brand
转型期，你说你的品牌一度
was stagnant at one point and then it
停滞不前，后来在
took off again when you made a lot of
你进行了很多
sort of operational changes and sort of
运营调整和
changes to the business model but at the
商业模式改革之后，它又重新腾飞了。 但
heart of the brand there was always
这个品牌的核心始终蕴藏着
something special you know to even be at
某种特别之处，你知道，它甚至能达到
six million revenue and I remember back
六百万美元的营收。我还记得
when I first discovered represent and
我第一次发现Represent这个品牌的时候，可能有些人
for anyone that doesn't know it's
还不知道，我
basically the only thing I wear so like
基本上只穿Represent的衣服。所以，
if you ever see me out or on stage or
如果你在外面、舞台上或者其他任何地方看到我，
whatever I'm wearing represent head to
我都会从头到脚穿着Represent的衣服。我的
toe I mean it's it's I wear this I
意思是，我平时不穿这身打扮，虽然
usually don't wear this on the podcast
在播客节目里我通常不穿，
but when I'm not on the podcast it's the
但除了播客节目，其他时候
only thing I'm wearing and the the 24/7
我都只穿Represent的衣服。
pants that you made are the only pants
你们设计的24/7裤子也是
that I wear everyone knows that like you
我唯一穿的裤子，大家都知道。你
know I don't actually have another pair
知道，我实际上没有其他裤子，到处都是Represent的衣服，
ofs that's all over um because there's
因为
something there when I discovered the
当我发现这个
brand there was always something special
品牌的时候，它就蕴藏着某种特别的东西。 它很特别，
about it and it's hard to explain right
很难解释清楚，对吧？
and when you observe the brand it's
当你观察这个品牌时，它
clearly turned into a bit of a cult
显然已经发展成一种类似邪教的存在，对吧？一种
right a good cult no one's getting
良性的邪教，没人因此
murdered it's a good cult but what is
丧命，它是一种良性的邪教。但是
that thing that the brand always had oh
这个品牌一直以来拥有的特质是什么呢？哦，这
that's hard that's a hard question it's
很难，这真是一个难题，
really hard I think it's the fact that
真的很难。我想，关键在于，
it's like two brothers that from
它是由两个来自
Manchester that don't really belong in
曼彻斯特的兄弟创立的，他们原本并不属于
fashion have come up and done this
时尚圈，却创造了如此
really cool thing where they're proven
酷炫的品牌，证明了
that we don't need to just follow the
我们不必
rule book and we can do whatever we want
墨守成规，我们可以做任何我们想做的事，
to do and sell whatever we want to sell
卖任何我们想卖的东西。
and like it's still even though it's a
即使现在它已经是一个
huge brand now it's still like a small
大品牌，它仍然保留着一些小众的
thing where like the Owners Club for
元素，比如它的“Owners Club”系列，就像是品牌
within it one range within it where like
内部的一个分支，
you see someone else wi an own's Club
你会看到有人穿着Owners Club的连
hoodie like you see them two guys not at
帽衫，你会看到那两个人，他们
each other and it's like yeah part of
彼此之间没有敌意，这就像是某种东西的一部分，
something like we've kind of built this
我们建立了一个
community that is it stems from the
社群，这个社群源于
people that are in the business but it's
业内人士。 它规模
so much bigger and it's on a global
庞大，业务遍及全球，
scale but it's still like pretty small
但同时又感觉很温馨，就像一家
and it's it's like a it's a family
家族
business right it's run by two brothers
企业，由两兄弟经营，
and everyone within the business feels
公司里的每个人都像
like family and when you buy a piece of
家人一样。当你购买我们的
that product we're giving them way more
产品时，我们给予你的远超预期。我最看重的就是
my main things is like quality and I
品质，我
want the customer to think um I follow
希望顾客会想：“嗯，我关注
these guys kind of cool I might try a
这家公司，感觉还不错，也许可以试试他们的连
hoodie and they get way more than they
帽衫。”然后他们得到的远超
expect and that's when like they become
预期，这时他们就会成为我们的忠实拥趸。
part of that cult you're exceeding their
我们超越了他们的
expectations exceeding their
期望，远远超出他们的
expectations way more than what they
想象。
thought it would but for you to exceed
但要超越
my expectations there must be something
我的期望，肯定有我们
going on in the office yeah that isn't
公司内部的运作机制。没错，
going on in the other fashion brands
其他时尚品牌
offices yeah and what is that thing
公司肯定做不到这一点。那么，
that's happening at represent that's
Represent究竟有什么秘诀，能让我们在
competitive place I think it's my innate
竞争对手那里脱颖而出呢？我想，这源于我内心深处想要做到
desire to just have just be the best
最好的渴望，
however we show up whether it's a popup
无论我们以何种方式呈现，无论
whether it's a run Club whether it's the
是快闪店、跑步俱乐部，还是
the feel of a garment or the delivery
服装的质感或配送
saying it's going to take three days and
服务。 有时候需要三天，有时候一天就搞定了。
it takes one day I think it's just my
我觉得这纯粹是我
innate desire to just really be the best
内心深处想要做到最好的愿望，毕竟
at how we show up as a brand
我们品牌的形象总是那么完美。这真的让人
exhausting because because the reason
筋疲力尽，因为
why people don't do that is because it's
人们不这么做的原因很简单，
easier to cut the corner right it's
偷工减料更容易，
easier to send it 3 days it's easier to
三天就发货更容易，对
not really care about the quality of
质量也更容易不在乎。当然，
course but like it's so personal to us
这对我们来说意义非凡，是
and it's all we were and it's all we
我们的一切，也是我们
obsess over every day so it's got to be
每天痴迷的事业，所以它必须做到
good what do people not see in terms of
最好。人们看不到
between you and your brother Michael
你和你哥哥迈克尔在工作中付出的努力，
they don't see Mike enough yeah I'm
他们看不到什么？他们看不到迈克尔的付出。是的，我一直在
trying to get him to come out more with
努力让他更多地分享
how how he does things and these process
他的工作方式和流程
and stuff but you like with him you're
等等。你
seeing a guy that is in a room designing
看到的是一个
all day every day with his Graphics team
每天都和他的平面设计团队待在房间里设计的人，
and it's not just him it's the full
而且这不仅仅是他一个人的功劳，而是整个业务的
scale of the business the logistics the
方方面面：物流、生产、
garments and like the content team like
服装设计团队等等。 内容团队的
all of them are so bought into it and
所有成员都非常投入，
everyone we bring up to the office
我们带回办公室的每个人，
whether it's a store or another brand or
无论是商店、其他品牌还是其他什么，都
whatever like they're [__] Blown Away
惊叹不已，他们简直
no one can believe what's going on in
不敢相信
there and it's this ecosystem that's
里面正在发生的一切。这是一个由
been built by spy and us as leaders and
我们和领导者共同打造的生态系统，我们
and really like bled this Mission into
真正将这种使命融入到
everyone that's in there that like we're
每个人的心中，让大家相信我们正在
creating something that's going to be
创造一些非凡的东西，一些比我们
lost ourselves when you've put so much
自己失去的东西更长久的东西。当你倾注了那么多
of your heart into the designs and then
心血设计，然后
you go on Instagram and someone's copied
你在Instagram上发现有人抄袭了
it yeah and it's your brother's design
它，而且抄袭的还是你兄弟的设计。
that they've copied and I see I see
我
people copying your stuff all the
经常看到有人抄袭你的东西，这怎么能算
time how's that it's good it means it
好事呢？这
means the Design's good right no that's
说明你的设计很棒，对吧？不，
not how you felt the first time no at
你第一次听到这种消息时可不是这么想的。一
first you [__] hate it and you think
开始你会非常讨厌，你会觉得
people are taking food off your table
有人在抢你的饭碗。
and in some cases that's right um and if
在某些情况下，确实如此。如果
if it's a brand that's like very similar
是一个和我们非常相似的品牌，
to us and they're trying to do the same
他们试图……
they're at the same price points as us
他们也做着同样的事情，价格和我们一样，
and they're in our market and they're
他们也在我们的市场，而且他们正在
taking market share then yeah it's like
抢占市场份额。是的，
they shouldn't be doing that and it'll
他们不应该这样做，最终会
bite them in the ass when it comes to it
自食其果。归根结底，关键在于谁能坚持到底，对吧？
it for the long run right copying other
模仿
people we used to do it when we we
别人，我们
started I'm not going to sit here and
创业初期也这么做过。我不会坐在这里
say everything was origin
说一切都是原创，
we've all been there and done that I
我们都经历过。
don't think I don't think when you're at
我不认为当你
a larger scale you do do it but then you
规模更大的时候，你会这么做，但你会
see brands that are huge High luxury
看到一些大型的高端
fashion brands go and do it to a small
时尚品牌去模仿小型
designer um so I think it's just it's
设计师。所以我觉得这就是
just what comes with life I'm sure
生活的一部分。我相信
you'll get it with podcasts it's the
你在播客里也会遇到这种情况，对吧？
same thing right you just got to laugh
你只能一笑置之。是的，
it yeah I've thought about how you know
我一直在思考，你知道，我
my journey with with people like copying
一路走来，一直在经历着人们模仿
what you do or whatever has been it's
你之类的事情，这确实是
been on a bit of a journey and it's
一个漫长的过程，而且很
difficult cuz it's because especially
艰难，因为尤其
when you care so much about something
当你很在意的时候。 很多时候，当
someone copies it it really hits you in
别人抄袭你的东西时，真的会在某种程度上触动你的
the heart to some degree it's like
内心，
especially if you can like remember
尤其是当你还记得自己最初是怎么想到这个
where you came up with that idea and
创意的时候。
then but I but you're right it's an
但是，你说得对，这是
inevitability and it's also um I always
不可避免的。而且，我总是
think about how the most important stuff
想，最重要的
is actually the part of the iceberg
其实是冰山
under the water yeah and even with
水面下的部分。即使是
design I I try and get this across to my
设计，我也努力让我的
team that like it's not even the design
团队明白，真正重要的不是设计本身，而是
really that counts it's the whole brand
整个品牌。
they're bu they're not buying into this
他们买单的不是这个
word yeah they're not buying into that
词，而是品牌的
they're buying into this essence of like
精髓——
them becoming part of this club and like
成为这个俱乐部的一员，
they're getting this Prestige and
获得声望，
getting the workouts and they're all
参与训练，融入
we're portraying and doing and living
我们所展现的生活方式。
and becoming the most important stuff
最重要的是，
they can't copy no one can copy that
他们无法复制的东西，没人能复制。他们
they can copy a logo and they can't copy
可以复制一个标志，但他们无法复制
like what what you stand for
你所代表的意义。
right so you've gone from being a
所以，你们从
million in 2018 to as we sit here now I
2018年年收入800万美元的公司，发展到如今的规模。 我
think last year you did about about 100
觉得你去年赚了大概一
million dollar yeah which is exceptional
亿美元，是的，这可是相当惊人的数字。
money is now um large in your life you
现在钱在你生活中占据了很重要的位置。
I'm sure you run the numbers and you go
我相信你肯定算过账，然后会想“妈的，我
[__] I'm worth this much money if I sold
值这么多钱，如果我卖掉它能卖多少钱”。
it for this [__] try not
尽量别这么想，
to but do you think uh do you think
但你觉得……你
about how do you think about money now
现在是怎么看待金钱的？
I'm not going to lie and sit here and
我不会撒谎说
say like oh money's not an issue money's
钱不是问题，钱
not a a thing that drives me because it
不是我的动力，因为它确实
is and I think it is with everyone and
是，而且我认为对每个人都一样。
I'll speak to billionaires and they'll
我跟亿万富翁们聊过，他们
say on camera
在镜头前会说
that they're doing it for this and they
他们是为了这个，为了
doing it for that and then they'll say
那个，然后他们会在
off camera like I want to get [__]
镜头外说“我想他妈的发财”。
Rich course I want to be rich everyone
当然，我也想发财，每个人都想发财。
negativity that comes with having a lot
拥有很多钱并没有什么负面影响。
of money and I think that society and
我认为现在的社会，以及人们对金钱的看法，好像
good thing that you're making a lot of
赚很多
money like I want I want represent to be
钱不是一件好事。但我想要，我想要代表着数
doing billions I want everyone in the
十亿美元的收入，我
business to be extremely wealthy I want
想要业内每个人都非常富有。
the leadership team to be able to have
领导团队能够拥有这样的
generational wealth like that that's
世代财富，这
first and foremost like I I like I love
首先也是最重要的，我喜欢，我喜欢这样，
that why not but if you had a billion
为什么不呢？但是，如果你现在拥有10亿
pounds now would you be any happier I I
英镑，你会更快乐吗？我
don't measure anything on happiness like
并不以幸福来衡量任何东西，比如，
I I'm I'm happy to sit in design for 6
我乐意坐在设计室里工作6个
hours or I'm happy to go for a run and
小时，或者我乐意去跑步，即使累得
like absolutely ruin my legs like that
腿都废了，这些都会
makes me happy I also like doing hard
让我快乐。我也喜欢挑战自我，
things and rewarding myself um and
并奖励自己。嗯，
that's NE that's not really money but
这和金钱无关，但就像
like like I said earlier money never has
我之前说的，金钱永远不会产生
a negative impact I don't
负面影响，我
think but on that point about giving you
认为。但是，说到给你
a billion dollars if I give you a
10亿英镑，如果我给你10
billion dollars and it's not going to
亿英镑，它却不会
make you any any happier then what's the
让你更快乐，那么这笔
point in the the money I think it will
钱有什么意义呢？我认为它会让
make me happier really yeah course dude
我更快乐，真的。当然，伙计，如果我的
I could my family would be set forever
家人和
all my team would be set forever like
我的团队都能从此衣食无忧，这
that in makes me happy imagine me being
会让我快乐。想象一下，我
able to turn up to my family and being
可以去见我的家人，说：“
okay Dad I know you've worked all your
爸爸，我知道你辛苦了一辈子，给你这个，好好
life here's here's this enjoy it what's
享受吧，还有什么？” 就
the exit strategy per se I don't know
退出策略本身而言，我不知道还有什么
anything else so why would I want to
其他选择，所以我为什么要
leave how are you going to get the
离开？
billion if you don't leave we'll do it
如果你不离开，你怎么赚到那十亿美元？我们会通过
profits um no I don't I don't want a I
利润来实现。嗯，不，我不需要，我
don't want a billion dollars in my bank
不想银行账户里有十亿美元，
account like that's not needed
那没必要。
but when you say what's the exit
但当你问我退出
strategy I'm like when I watched you
策略是什么时，我就会想，当我看到你
leave your business I was always
离开你的公司时，我总是
thinking like you already had the the
觉得你已经安排好了
podcast lined up and you're already
播客，而且你已经
ready to move into this thing anyway so
准备好投入到这件事中，所以这
it made sense for you I don't have that
对你来说很合理。我没有这些，
and I also don't want that like I love
我也不想要。我热爱
represent I wake up and it's represent
代表，我醒来时，它代表着
everything everything I talk to about
一切，我谈论的一切，
everyone is the brand everything I do is
每个人，我做的每件事，都是我的品牌。
the brand that what like even bringing
甚至把
my fitness into this thing is my brand
我的健身理念融入到这件事中，也是我的品牌。
and like I've been able to then build
我能够把
247 into this brand which is actually
247打造成这个品牌，这对
me than um than building a business and
我来说更像是一个充满激情的项目，而不是一个商业项目。
even though like all the athletes that
尽管所有
are involved like I'm able to suck so
参与其中的运动员，我都能从他们身上汲取
much like knowledge and worth out of
很多知识和价值，这对我个人来说也很重要。 所以，
business doesn't make sense when your
当你的
identity and your profession become so
身份和职业如此
intrinsically
紧密地
linked there's a cost to that right
联系在一起时，转行或者直接卖掉公司就显得毫无意义了。这其中是有代价的，对吧？
because it must feel you know you talked
因为你肯定感觉很糟，你知道，你之前说过，
if the revenue started to Plum it and it
如果品牌走下坡路，收入开始暴跌，不再流行，或者
went out of Vogue or whatever they call
不管他们怎么称呼
it like it just was no not popular
它，只要不再受欢迎，
anymore that's linked to your like
那会是什么感觉？这百分之百地与你的自尊、
self-esteem and you're like self-worth
自我价值
and your
和
identity 100% and look there is days
身份认同息息相关。你看，有时候业绩
where it doesn't do well there is still
不好，
days now where we'll launch products and
现在也一样，我们推出新产品，结果却惨不忍睹。说
that feel honestly it [__] with you
实话，那种感觉有多糟糕？它会打击
[__] with your confidence um but it
你的自信心。但它
also gives you a realization that you're
也让你意识到，你
not super human and you can't do
不是超人，你不可能事事亲力亲为，也不是每次都能
turns to gold and then you got to go
点石成金，然后你就得重新开始。那会是什么感觉？
you think about the last time it
你会回想上次
happened how did it feel and how long
发生这种情况时的感受，
did that feeling last it lasts a few
那种感觉持续了多久？ 这种情况会持续
days and I'll speak to Spenny about it a
几天，我会在这几天里和斯潘尼（Spenny）聊
lot over them few days and he'll
很多，他会
reassure that something else is going to
安慰我说会有其他事情让我
take that feeling away from it and it
摆脱这种感觉，
usually does and as well like it it's
通常也确实如此。而且，人生
not all about small failures along the
并非只有小小的挫折，还有
way and there's so many exciting things
很多令人兴奋的事情。所以，
that when something small trips you up a
当一些小事让你稍微受挫时，
little bit you've got to realize like no
你必须意识到，
this is for the long term like the
这是为了长远发展，是为了
future is this is in 10 years let's look
未来，是为了十年后回首往事，把它看作是一个
back at this as like a a learning curve
学习的过程。
amongst all of this you've still got to
在这一切之中，你仍然需要
figure out how to have a life like a
找到自己的生活，拥有
personal life because regardless of how
个人生活。因为无论
intrinsically connected you are to the
你与
brand represent you're still going to
代表的品牌联系多么紧密，你仍然
need to have a life you're still going
需要拥有自己的生活，你仍然
to need to be a George in there
需要以乔治（George）的身份存在于你的生活中。是的，在
for a long time past 10 years I've not
过去的十年里，我几乎没有
really had a
过自己的
life not nothing outside of represent
生活，除了代表品牌之外，我什么都没有。
but I've built repres into my life in
但我已经把代表品牌融入到我的生活中。
the moment I think about you know times
回想我
in my career where I was absolutely all
职业生涯中的某些时期，我全身心投入到
in on something to the point that I was
某件事中，甚至
like seven days a week in this [__]
一周七天都投入其中。 在这该死的
office and even the weekends when
办公室里，甚至周末
there's nothing to do I'm just in there
没事干的时候，我也待在那儿，
cuz I got new mates dude so that's when
因为我交了新朋友。所以那时候
I realized so them Sundays where you'd
我才意识到，那些星期天，你一个人
be sat at home on your own no one would
待在家里，没人会给
be messaging you you can't do anything
你发消息，你没法
with people in the business because it's
和公司里的人一起做任何事，因为那是
their time off with the families that's
他们和家人一起休息的时间。那时候
when I realized like [__] I'm like I'm
我才意识到，操，我
probably too bought into this were you
可能太投入了。你会感到
lonely alone but never lonely never I
孤独吗？我从来不会感到孤独，从来没有。
where I felt lonely may maybe a little
我从来没有感到过孤独，也许会有一点点，
bit but like I would I would distract
但我会用
myself with going working out for five
锻炼五个
hours you
小时来分散注意力，
know or just putting my headphones in
或者戴上耳机
and listening to a book and just just
听书，就这样来回走走，
Sunday's done anyway Sundays were my
星期天就过去了。反正星期天是我
worst days because I didn't have anyone
最难熬的日子，因为我没人陪我。我会去
like I'd go I'd go and train at a local
当地一家
gym where there's a big Community there
健身房锻炼，那里有个很大的社群，
for the from 6:00 a.m. till 9:00 a.m.
从早上6点到9点。
and I come home I just sit there and
然后我回家就坐在那儿，
think when's it Monday isn't that funny
想着星期一什么时候来。 是不是很搞笑？我发
text my mom like what you up to and she
短信问我妈在干嘛，她
be like oh we're actually up in Scotland
会说哦，我们其实在苏格兰
doing this trip I be like [__] I can't
旅行呢。我就会想，我去，我
even go and see my
连见我
mom so yeah I guess I guess there is a
妈都去不了。所以，我想，我想，我心里肯定有点
little bit of loneliness in there yeah I
孤独吧。是啊，我
was lonely but I didn't know it at the
当时很孤独，但我自己没意识到。是啊，我
time yeah I only know it in hindsight
只有在事后回想的时候才明白，
cuz I look back at the way I was living
因为我会审视自己当时的生活方式。
and right yeah I was filling the Gap the
没错，我一直在填补
Sunday Saturday Summer evenings holidays
周日、周六、夏日夜晚、假期，
even Christmases like cuz I was in
甚至是圣诞节的空档。因为我在
Manchester my family are in the
曼彻斯特，而我的家人在
southwest I was filling it with work
西南部，所以我用工作填满这些时间，而且
like often just like pointless work
经常是一些毫无意义的工作，
absolutely unneeded stuff a lot of the
完全没必要。很多时候，
time it's it's great and you can go out
这感觉很棒，你可以出去，
and you can spend a few hours on your
可以独自待几个小时，
own and write a load of things down that
写下一大堆下周要做的事情，
you need to do that next week or but you
或者说你
need a team to do
需要一个团队才能完成
anything like I can't get anything done
任何事情，没有团队我什么都做不了。这就是
thing I would realize every weekend that
我每个周末都会意识到的一件事：
like I'm wasting my time pretending to
我是在浪费时间假装
work it's exactly what I was
工作。我当时就是在
doing relationships romantic
做这些，还有恋爱
relationships let's start with
关系。 我们先从
non-romantic relationships in fact you
非恋爱关系说起。事实上，你
talk about having to shed people in
提到过要摆脱那些对你产生
terms of like negative influences in
负面影响的人，
order to change your
才能改变
life people ask me about this all the
生活。人们总是问我这个问题，是的，
time which is yeah you know how
你知道
important is the environment on personal
环境对个人
and professional success I think it's
和职业成功有多重要。我认为环境
everything I think your ecosystem that
至关重要。
you build around you is everything
你围绕自己构建的生态系统决定一切，
whether that's the distance it takes you
无论是
to get to the gym or the people you
去健身房的路程，还是你
follow on social media if you're
在社交媒体上关注的人。如果你
following Joe from school that's out
关注的是学校里那个每天晚上出去喝酒的乔，
them stories even if it's 20 seconds of
即使你每天只花20秒看他的动态，也是在
your day you're wasting your time
浪费时间。
watching them stories and you're also
而且你
looking at things that are just
关注的都是
absolutely pointless to your life so why
对你的生活毫无意义的东西。所以，为什么
don't you go and follow someone who's
不去关注那些已经
done what you want to do or he's doing
实现了你的目标，或者正在做
what you want to do or who actually
你想做的事情，或者真正
inspires you and just clear out all the
激励你的人呢？把所有
[__] and you you're going to be so
无意义的事情都清除掉，你的心态就会好得多。
space if you do something like
如果
that did you do that did you clear out
你这样做，你清理过那些负面影响吗？是的，我清理过
yeah did it a lot of
很多
times got a lot of bad messages from
次，也接触过很多不好的东西。
doing it really
真的吗，
Jo okay yeah why did you unfollow me do
Jo？好吧，是的，你为什么取关我？
you explain it to him um yeah just tell
你跟他解释过吗？嗯，就直接告诉
them how it is
他们，就说“
just say look man I don't want to watch
伙计，我不想再看
you sit anymore so romantic
你坐着了”。
relationships then how has that been
那么，恋爱关系呢？因为要
have to maintain a healthy happy
维持一段健康快乐的
romantic relationship nonexistent didn't
恋爱关系，肯定很棘手，因为你必须投入大量的精力。我以前从来
didn't entertain it for so many years
没有过恋爱关系，这么多年来都没考虑过。
once maybe like when I was 25 26 and
可能在我25、26岁的时候试过一次，但就是
just didn't work Why didn't it work I
不行。为什么行不通？因为我当时
was obsessed with work and I was also
沉迷于工作，而且我
I didn't know who I was and what I
不知道自己是谁，也不知道自己想成为什么样的人。那是在
before that time of mine where I changed
我改变之前，在我经历那个阶段之前。
so it just I didn't like who I was and
我不喜欢当时的自己，很
obviously that doesn't work when you're
明显，这样是行不通的。当你
in a relationship you got to you got to
谈恋爱的时候，你必须
love yourself first right MH um and then
先爱自己，对吧？嗯，在那之后，
after that I just kind of just said no
我就直接说“不，
I'm not doing it and didn't up until
我不谈恋爱了”，直到
recently really didn't entertain it at
最近才开始考虑。
all for so many years you got a
这么多年来，你有没有
girlfriend have I no not not really kind
女朋友？没有，真的没有。
of would she answer this question the
她会用同样的方式回答这个问题吗？
same way she got a boyfriend she's got a
她有男朋友了，她有
boyfriend no are you a little bit um are
男朋友了。不，你有点……嗯……
you you're an avoidant aren't you do you
你是回避型依恋吗？你
know the the attachment Styles have you
知道依恋类型吗？你
heard about the attachment Styles no
听说过依恋类型吗？没有。那是
what's that three attachment Styles
什么？三种依恋类型，
you've got the secures they're the ones
安全型，他们
that just have the perfect relationships
拥有完美的关系，对吧？
right you know they're like no problems
你知道，他们就像没有问题一样，
they're like you know and then you've
你知道的。然后是
got the anxious ones who clingy like
焦虑型，他们很粘人，需要……需要……需要
need like they need like need attention
关注，对，
yeah exactly and then you've got the
没错。然后是
avoidant who kind of run right strike me
回避型，他们有点逃避，对吧？我觉得自己是
as an avoidant um I don't know what I am
回避型，嗯……我不知道我是什么，
I don't I I really don't know I'm
我真的不知道，我
definitely not an attachment one no um
肯定不是依恋型，不，嗯……
and I just always thought it would
我只是觉得那样会给
be a pressure on myself to then and I
我带来压力，我不想
because of what I was doing with work
因为我的工作
and I don't want to have to explain to
而让别人失望，我不想在别人想见你的时候，不得不向他们解释“
someone like this is my business this is
这是我的事业，这是
my life I'm doing this all the time when
我的生活，我一直在做这些”。
they want to see you and they want they
他们想见你，他们想……他们
want your attention and stuff but now
想…… 你的注意力等等，但现在
like hiring spany and having more time
就像雇佣了 Spany，有了更多的时间，
and actually coming moving out here I've
实际上搬到这里后，我
got time now like my day is done way
现在有时间了，我的一天结束得比以前在家时早得多。
before what it was at home I would work
我会在家工作，
from or i' train and then I would work
或者训练，然后再在家工作。我
from I'd be in the office at half 5 in
早上 5 点半到办公室，晚上
the morning I'd leave at 7:00 p.m. and
7 点离开。
I'd go to bed so there was no time but
我以前会早早睡觉，所以没时间，但
now I can wake up early get all the
现在我可以早起，和
stuff done with the guys at home work
家里的兄弟们一起把所有事情做完，
with the guys over here building out
和这边的兄弟们一起建设
representing LA and then I can be done
洛杉矶，然后我
by like 2 3 p p.m. a lot of days so I
大概下午两三点就能完成所有事情了。 很多天我都有时间，所以有时间去做一些约会之类的事情，比如约会
goals and
目标之类的，
things like that and how's that going
但感觉如何？
hate it really no not I hate it I guess
真的讨厌这样，不，我讨厌这样。我想
guess you do hate it because I was I
你肯定也讨厌这样，因为我总觉得
where I'm not fulfilling what I should
我没有尽到自己应该
be doing and I'm kind of giving myself a
做的事情，
disservice if I'm out doing something
如果我出去做其他事，就好像在亏待自己。
else and I think a lot of entrepreneurs
我觉得很多创业者
and people who run businesses get that
和经营企业的人都有这种感觉，
where like if you're not fully into the
如果你没有全身心投入到
business like with every minute of your
事业中，每一分钟
time you feel like you're not doing the
你都会觉得自己没有做
right thing and I'm I'm starting to try
对。我开始努力
and get out like a guilt feelings yes
摆脱这种内疚感，是的，
very guilty yeah and that actually
非常内疚。这实际上
caused me a little bit of what we think
让我有点焦虑，
is anxiety I don't know if it is anxiety
我不知道是不是焦虑，
but it really yeah yeah I would wake up
但确实如此。第二天醒来，我会想：妈的，我竟然花了
spend four hours with this person that
四个小时和一个
I'm not interested in seeing that's I've
我根本不想见的人在一起，我
wasted four hours where I could have
浪费了四个小时，本来我可以
been working could have been building
工作，可以打造
the brand could have been doing other
品牌，可以做其他
things sounds like a lot when I say a
事情。我说
lot I mean like a lot of a weight to
很多，是真的很多。 背负着沉重的负担，是
carry yeah like to not be able to go on
啊，就像不能
a date with someone for four hours
和某人约会四个小时，
without waking up the next day feeling
第二天醒来就会
anxious about how you spent your time it
焦虑自己如何度过时间。
feels like your passions become a bit of
感觉自己的爱好变成了某种牢笼，是的，
a prison yeah a self-inflicted prison
自我囚禁。
but I love it and and it's a privilege
但我热爱它，拥有它是一种荣幸。
to have it but I'm I'm starting learning
但我正在学习，
like I said I'm kind of got a girlfriend
就像我说的，我现在有点儿女朋友了，
right now um kind of got a girlfriend
嗯，有点儿女朋友，
you're in so much trouble you have no
你麻烦大了，你根本不
idea that's
知道。
fine she's oh George is on a podcast I
没关系，她……哦，乔治上了一个播客，我
have listen to this she's going to click
得听听，她会点开的。我们会在
it we'll do a chapter on YouTube which
YouTube上做一个章节，
is called George's girlfriend we'll put
叫做《乔治的女朋友》，我们会把
it in the trailer you're going to be
它放在预告片里。你肯定会惹上大
some serious trouble absolutely fine
麻烦，绝对没问题。
Valentine's day yesterday and you're
昨天是情人节，你却把她
throwing under the
出卖了，真有意思。
bus interesting but it does it sounds it
但听起来确实有点像
sounds like a little bit of a prison
坐牢，是
yeah you know um not being able to take
啊，你知道，嗯，一刻也不能
your foot off the pedal at all without
放松，否则就会
feeling anxious MH are you happy yeah
焦虑。MH，你快乐吗？是的，那
and what does that mean that means I I
意味着什么？这意味着我
wake up I'm [__] thankful for what
醒来后，我他妈的感激……
I've got and what I've built and who I'm
我拥有的一切，我所建立的一切，我
around and like my brother and my family
身边的人，比如我的兄弟和家人，
and like I enjoy being able to just do
我享受能够做自己
what I want to do and that is the work I
想做的事，而这大概就是我大部分时间都在做的事情。
guess most of the time you know when
你知道，当
people talk about work life balance M
人们谈论工作与生活平衡时，
what's your honest opinion of that
你对这种胡扯有什么真实看法？
[__] if you actually want to build
如果你真的想打造
something that's going to stand the test
一些经得起
of time and make you very successful and
时间考验、让你非常成功、
Rich and happy and bring other people
富有、快乐，并且能够带动其他人
with you it's going to take everything I
一起发展的东西，那就需要付出一切。我
fully believe that I don't think you can
完全相信这一点。我认为你不能
half ass it I don't think it can be a
敷衍了事，它不能只是个
side project and I don't think it can be
副业，也不能
something that's just 3 hours a day I
每天只花三个小时。我
think you've got to go fully into it to
认为你必须全身心投入，才能
become like high level achiever like
成为真正的成功者，成为高水平的成就者。
winner what are you willing to sacrifice
你愿意为此牺牲什么？
for that everything whatever it takes
一切，无论付出什么代价，
why not I'm already into it now so I've
为什么不呢？我现在已经投入其中了，所以我必须全力以赴。你
got to got to go fall on look Kobe
看，科比·
Bryant wasn't doing three throws at
布莱恩特凌晨三点投篮可不是无缘无故的。
you got to be the best you got to do
你必须做到最好，你必须全力以赴。
everything right I always talk about the
一切都好，我总是谈到随之而来的
cost that comes with that and the
代价和
sacrifice are you willing to sacrifice
牺牲。你愿意牺牲
you not having a family yourself for the
自己暂时没有家庭吗？是的，也许
time being yeah maybe later on in life
以后，当
when it when it
它
becomes something that I can step aside
成为我可以完全抽身的事情时，
from even more then yeah you're going to
你会
want to step aside from it because
想要抽身的，因为
you're getting anxiety doing 4our dates
你会因为约会而感到焦虑。但我正在
how you but I'm learning I'm learning
学习，我正在学习，
I'm starting to do it like I said yeah
我开始做到了。就像我说的，是的，
you've seen progress in that definitely
你在这方面确实取得了进步。是的，
yeah I think it's just about building
我认为这只是在培养
that muscle of understanding you can do
这种理解能力，让你明白你可以做
other things and realizing it's not
其他事情，并且意识到
going to come crashing down if you take
即使你放松一下，它也不会崩溃，
your foot off the break for a second but
但你
still knowing that you're giving it your
仍然要知道，当
all when you are in
你全力以赴的时候，你仍然会全力以赴。
it is there a point where I always think
我总是会想到
about bbery as an example the bbery
Berry的例子，Berry的
story of how they kind of went out of
故事，它们是如何
fashion because they became too popular
因为太受欢迎而逐渐过时的。
what I'm trying to say is like bbery was
我想说的是，Berry曾经是一种令人向往的东西，
aspirational so lots of people start
所以很多人开始
wearing in it some less aspirational
穿它，一些不那么追求名利的
people start wearing it people start
人也开始穿它，有人开始
knocking it off and selling it for super
仿制它，并
cheap in markets then eventually it's no
在市场上以极低的价格出售，最终…… 它
longer aspirational right because
不再是人们向往的潮流，对吧？因为
because of because it got so popular
它太流行了，反而
that it becomes uncool is do you worry
变得不酷了。你会担心
about that as a risk factor for
这会成为Represent的风险因素吗？这
represent so that's like a life cycle
就像一个生命周期，
right and that comes every couple years
每隔几年
or every seven years whatever they may
或七年就会出现一次，无论
be in the industry but there's always
行业内的情况如何。总会有
different markets to push and pull on
不同的市场需要开拓和拉动。
also like represent is so small in terms
而且，Represent
of size compared to burbury at the
目前的规模与Burbury相比非常小，
moment we have a very core customer base
我们拥有一个非常核心的客户群，
where we kind of can identify them and
我们可以识别他们，
we know where they are and what they're
知道他们在哪里，在
doing and until that goes mainstream
做什么。直到它成为主流，
which I think usually happens probably
我认为这通常发生在
Revenue um I don't it's not a worry as
营收达到2.5亿到3亿美元的时候。嗯，目前我并不担心。
such at the moment I used to worry about
我以前很担心，
a lot but like when Spenny came in he
但当Spenny加入时，他
was handling a $500 million business
管理着一个5亿美元的业务，
he's like we're barely touching the
他说我们
sides 20% of our revenues in the US
在美国的收入只占总收入的20%，也
that's only $20 million they could sell
就是2000万美元。他们可能
$20 million out of LA and not see the
在洛杉矶卖出2000万美元的
product for the next six months you
产品，但在接下来的六个月里都
wouldn't even see someone wearing it so
看不到有人穿。所以，
at this point no but it it is something
目前我不会担心。 这是
that we will always think about and
我们一直都会考虑的问题，
always you've always got to limit your
你必须始终限制
distribution and make sure you're
分销渠道，确保
selling it in the right places and look
在合适的地方销售。你看，
we are still like a luxury brand we
我们仍然是一个奢侈品牌，我们在
we're in the best stores in the world
世界上最好的商店里销售，
like it's not like you can walk into a
不像其他品牌那样，你可以随便走进一家便利
Pon and pick us up so it's it's still
店就能买到。所以它仍然
not a mainstream brand and it's
不是主流品牌，而且价格
expensive I was wondering if it if
昂贵。我在想，这
that's less of a threat in on the 247
在24/7全天候销售
side of things where it's more about
领域是否构成威胁，因为24/7更注重
like utility and less about like fashion
实用性而非时尚性，
because you know everyone wears Nike
你知道，每个人都穿耐克，
yeah and no one's like oh my God I'm not
没人会说“天哪，我竟然
wearing Nike because they're wear it you
没穿耐克”，因为他们都在穿。你
know yeah biggest Sports we brand in the
知道，耐克是世界上最大的运动品牌，
world and how are they able to tier a
他们怎么能把
Travis Scott or a virgila blow Jordan
Travis Scott或Virgil Abloh Jordan联名
one that's going for $5,000 but they're
款卖到5000美元，但他们
still selling tracksuits at $20 and you
仍然以20美元的价格出售运动服，你
can still see everyone in Gold's Gym to
仍然可以看到从Gold's Gym到Equinox健身房的每个人都在
everyone in [__] Equinox wearing it
穿耐克，
so there's there's just te to everything
所以一切都存在问题，对吧？ 涓滴效应
right there's a trickle down system with
渗透到方方面面，
everything I wonder if that's is that
我很好奇这是否是
because it's like more of your utility
因为它更像是实用
product than a fashion product I think
产品而非时尚产品。我觉得
so with Nike yeah definitely um because
耐克就是这样，没错，因为
it's not really like a fashion brand
它不像其他时尚品牌那样
that's able to sell like a $20 item and
能卖出20美元的单品。
then like a Ralph Lauren oh really do
而像拉夫·劳伦，哦，真的吗？
they so cheap and expensive stuff well
他们既有便宜的也有贵的。
if you look at Ralph Lauren most like it
如果你看看拉夫·劳伦，你会发现它的外观非常
looks amazing from the outside and they
漂亮，
the best the best spots in London and
在伦敦、
New York and la and most of their
纽约和洛杉矶等地的黄金地段都拥有许多精美的门店。他们的大部分
revenues done through Outlet at $20
收入都来自奥特莱斯，比如20美元
polos or $15 polos 60% of their sales is
或15美元的polo衫。据说polo衫占他们销售额的60%，
a polo top which I'm not I'm not exactly
我不太
sure on but that's what I hear so
确定这个数字，但这是我听说的。所以，
there's ways you
你
can I guess smoke and mirror it disguise
可以用一些花招来掩盖
things and do other things but for us
真相，或者做其他事情。但对我们
like we we're pretty solid on where we
来说，我们对
want to be in terms of the marketplace
市场定位
and the price points and we'll grow that
和价格点非常明确，我们会沿着这个方向发展，而
way rather than having to teer things
不是为了迎合市场而改变策略。我认为
to an extent what are the most important
最重要的是什么？
because I think most people will be
因为我想大多数人都会
listening to this conversation in
关注这一点。 这场对话的
essence because they want to know how
本质是，他们想知道
you've done what you've done you know
你是如何做到这一切的。他们想
they want to know like the transferable
知道，是什么
principles behind how it's possible
原则可以
to scale a very successful business that
推广到如此成功的企业，
also is unique because it's quite a cult
而且你的企业非常独特，因为它有点
business you've got like an incredibly
像邪教组织，拥有一个极具邪教
cultish brand you know you do like run
色彩的品牌。你知道，你经营
clubs and almost a thousand people will
俱乐部，街角会有近千人
show up on the street corner or you you
聚集，或者你一
drop something and you sell thousands in
发布新品，几分钟内就能卖出几千件。那么，
principles that you would maybe say to a
你会把哪些原则告诉一个
18yearold George or to that kid in your
18岁的年轻人，或者告诉你
DMs that's asking for the the
私信里那个问你这些
principles principles that only you
原则的年轻人？这些原则只有你
could have learned in hindsight I think
才能在事后领悟到。我认为关键在于
it's about creating the DNA of what the
打造
brand is and sticking to that not
品牌的DNA，并坚持
vearing off in different directions and
下去，而不是偏离方向，
based on Trends so I think it's about
根据潮流频繁地改变一切。我认为关键在于
holding a DNA where that's through thick
坚守品牌的DNA，无论顺境逆境，无论
and thin so whether it's not right for
它是否符合
that time or it is right for that time
当下的潮流。
fashion and things will go out and in
时尚总是有生命周期的，有些东西会过时，有些东西会流行，
fashion but if you can kind of cultivate
但如果你能培养出这种风格，它就能经久不衰。
the look that you want that's that's
你想要的就是这个，这才是最重要的。
first and foremost what it is like if
如果
you look at 247 and represent 247 looks
你看看 247 和 Represent，你会发现 247 看起来
like represent but it's active we it's
很像 Represent，但它更活跃，
not like it's a whole different thing
它不像 Lululemon 那样完全不同，它
that looks like Lululemon like it still
仍然保留了
looks like represent so I think making
Represent 的风格。所以我认为，
sure the DNA in the brand is very like
确保品牌的 DNA 清晰可见至关重要。那么，这个
visible where does the DNA come from
DNA 源自哪里呢？是
just personal preference what we like to
个人喜好吗？我们喜欢
wear what I what I feel like I look good
穿什么？我觉得自己穿什么好看？
in what Mike feels like he looks good in
Mike 觉得他穿什么好看？
what the team love and just building
团队成员喜欢什么？然后一步一步地建立起来，
creating products that we feel like is
创造出我们觉得
either missing or we just want for
缺失的或者我们自己想
wear and what would you say about hard
穿的产品。作为校长，你如何看待努力工作？
work as a principal I think it's
我认为努力工作至关重要，
everything I really do think it's
我真的认为它
everything I meet a lot of people
至关重要。我遇到过很多人，
especially out here that have their
尤其是在这里，他们涉足
little hands in different businesses
不同的行业，
lots of different pies but but don't
很多不同的领域，但他们对
work hard at any of them and none of
任何一个领域都不努力，结果
them really ever succeed or they only
他们都没有真正成功，或者
own 1% when you find out they've sold a
当你发现他们卖掉公司时，他们只拥有 1% 的股份。
business um so I think it's all about
所以我认为，关键在于
like going all in on something that you
全力以赴地投入到你所
own I think it's hard if you were just a
拥有的事业中。 我觉得如果你只是某个
small minority shareholder in something
小股东，那
like that then is not really your
确实很难，因为那不是你的
passion it's someone else's or it's a
热情所在，而是别人的，或者说是一
big group of
大群
peoples but when people think about hard
人的。但当人们想到努力
work they you know and people advise
工作时，他们会
someone and say you have to work hard if
说，如果
you want to be successful people say
你想成功就必须努力工作，有人会说
that's toxic yeah don't
这很毒。是啊，不管
care what what's
什么
toxic that word that word is just makes
毒，这个词本身就
no sense you're going to encourage
毫无意义，它只会让人
people to be burnt out yeah I think you
精疲力竭。不过，我认为你
can come out the other side of burnt out
可以从精疲力竭的状态中走出来，
like the more you do right the more you
就像你做得越多，你
can do so if you're working hard at
能做的也就越多。所以，如果你在努力做
something and you're starting to feel
某件事，开始觉得
like it's getting a bit too much the
有点吃不消，
pressure is a bit too much you carry on
压力有点大，那就继续
doing it you're going to come out of it
做下去，你会走出来的。事情不会就此结束，没有什么会结束，
just going to end nothing ends you just
你只是会
figure out different ways to actually
找到不同的方法让它
make it successful or you'll something
成功，或者你会找到一些有效的方法，然后
will work and you'll be like oh [__]
你会想“哦，天哪”，
then your energy goes back up and you
你的精力又会恢复，然后你又会重新投入，
start going down there and and it works
而且它真的有效。
I don't
我不
think I don't know I think there's a lot
认为 我不知道，我觉得现在关于
of negativity around working hard and I
努力工作有很多负面情绪，我
don't like that there's there's going to
不喜欢这样。
be a kid listening right now that's like
现在肯定有个16、18岁的孩子在听，
18 16 and they just can't find the
他们找不到
motivation whatever that means they
动力，不管这意味着什么，就是
can't find the motivation to get up and
找不到动力起床去
go to the gym they've got some idea but
健身房。他们可能有一些想法，但这些想法还放在
it's still on the sofa that they had it
沙发上。
on um like what what what do you say to
嗯，你会对
that young man or
这个年轻人说什么呢？
woman is the first thing to get the the
首先，要让他
wheels in motion [__]
行动起来，什么动力，去他的！
motivation I don't have motivation a lot
很多时候我也没有动力，
of time it's actually more about
其实更重要的是
discipline it's about just getting it
自律，是把事情
done get up and get it done like with
做完。起床，然后去做。就像
anything with work with working out with
任何事情一样，工作、锻炼、
creating a product with building a brand
创造产品、打造品牌、
with relationships whatever it's
人际关系等等，
discipline over motivation motivation is
自律比动力更重要。动力可能只是
a small thing that can last 2 minutes or
一小会儿，持续两分钟，也可能持续
an hour motivation can come from
一个小时。动力可能来自
listening to a a song on your
听iPod里的一首歌。
iPod if you got discipline you're
如果你有自律，你
willing to do it every single day of
愿意每天都去做，即使你
your life and knowing that it's going to
知道这需要
take so long to do it you just get up
很长时间，你也会起床去做。
and do it you don't even think about
你甚至都没想过
motivation and and what is and what is
动机是什么，也没想过什么是
discipline then discipline
自律。自律
is an instruction manual like what is
就像一本使用手册，
discipline to you yeah I guess it is an
对你来说自律是什么？嗯，我想它就是一本
instruction manual I guess it's a list
使用手册，它列出了
of things that you must do for yourself
你必须为自己做的事情，
to to become what you want to be
才能成为你想成为的人。
and it's I guess it's a deciding factor
我想它决定了
on whether you're going to do something
你是否要做某件事。这
about like you drew a picture of
就像你之前说的，你画了一幅
yourself of what you wanted to look like
自己理想形象的画像，
but you also wrote out like a set of
同时你也写下了一套
principles or values that you wanted to
你想践行的原则或价值观。然后
embody yeah and then you're living your
你就
life by that as opposed to how you feel
按照这些原则生活，而不是按照你每天的感觉生活。
every day yeah yeah when you put it that
嗯，这么说没错，它就是这样。
eventually it becomes part of them it
最终它会成为你的一部分，
know they say like habits what is it
就像肌肉一样，你会不断锻炼这块肌肉，不断地分解它，然后再重建它。这些原则最终会成为你的生活。你知道，人们常说习惯，是什么呢？
thoughts become habits and then habits
想法会变成习惯，习惯会
become principles and that becomes you
变成原则，最终塑造你这个
person a lot of people just don't think
人。很多人不认为
they're moldable goes back to what we
自己是可以塑造的，这就像我们
were saying earlier about like we just
之前说的，我们就是
don't think that we can change ourselves
不…… 我觉得我们可以改变自己，是的，
yeah but you your evidence of that
但是你有什么证据证明这一点吗？
really remarkable evidence of
真的非常了不起的证据。是的，有
that yeah and there's a lot of people
很多这样的人，
stories out there on social media and in
社交媒体、
books and podcasts and stuff that all
书籍、播客等等上面有很多鼓舞人心的故事，
these people that have completely
这些人彻底
changed their lives it just takes a lot
改变了自己的人生。这需要大量的
of time and a lot of effort are you
时间和努力。你有
confident I'm I'm not going to lie I
信心吗？说实话，我
lot of the time especially in business
很多时候仍然会怀疑一些事情，尤其是在商业方面。
but with myself yeah I'm I'm conf
但是对自己，是的，我有信心。
what do you have doubts about in
你在商业方面有什么疑虑吗？
business just like you said before maybe
就像你之前说的，也许有
one day the the revenue stops maybe one
一天收入会停止，也许有
day it gets too popular maybe one day
一天它会变得太受欢迎，也许有一天
something doesn't work
某些事情会
out maybe one day a competitor comes up
失败，也许有一天竞争对手会突然出现，
at the side of you and starts taking
抢走你的
everything from you the key to growing a
一切。发展
business is making sure that it's
业务的关键在于确保其可
scalable and this comes with integrating
扩展性，这需要
into the right platforms early in the
尽早整合到合适的平台
game to support your growth a platform
来支持你的增长。
that's helped me and my team to do this
帮助我和我的团队做到这一点的平台
is Shopify who I'm sure you know by now
是Shopify，我相信你现在应该知道了，
because they do sponsor this podcast
因为他们赞助了这个播客。Shopify
Shopify is a Commerce platform
是一个电商平台，正在
revolutionizing millions of businesses
革新全球数百万家企业的运营模式。
worldwide we recently launched our
我们最近推出了 我们
cards on Shopify which would not have
在 Shopify 上推出了第二版 Derio 对话卡片，如果
been possible without Shopify when I
没有 Shopify，这一切都不可能实现。当初我
started podcasting an online store was
开始做播客的时候，开网店是
the furthest thing from my mind but now
我最想不到的事情。但现在，
thanks to how simple it is to use the
多亏了
platform it's made this whole process so
这个平台的易用性，整个流程变得
unbelievably easy it's actually the
无比轻松。它实际上是
internet's best converting checkout 36%
互联网上转化率最高的平台，
better on average compared to other
平均比其他
leading Commerce platforms if you guys
领先的电商平台高出 36%。如果你
haven't tried Shopify on your business
还没在你的企业里尝试过 Shopify，
owners go and try it now because you can
现在就去试试吧，因为你只需
just by heading to shopify.com
访问 shopify.com
Bartlet and you can get started for $1
Bartlet 就能注册，享受每月 1 美元的试用期，然后就可以以 1 美元的价格开始使用。
What if Michael turned around and said
如果 Michael 突然说：“
you know what I'm done he just said I
你知道吗，我受够了。” 他说：“我
just can't do this anymore I I'm going
再也做不下去了，我……
to just you know I'm done um i' probably
你知道吗，我受够了。” 我可能
cry really yeah definitely um and I just
会哭，真的，肯定会哭。然后我会
try and figure out why what it is and
努力弄清楚原因，
then try and get him back in he said no
试图让他回来。但他却说：“不，我受够了。” 然后就结束了，
forever it had suck it would suck a lot
永远结束了。这太糟糕了，真的太糟糕了。
um because I've been since school we've
因为我从学生时代就开始
been together doing this forever so for
一起做这件事了，我们一直在一起做这件事。 如果
him then not to be
他不在，
be he'd be pretty shitty because like
他会非常沮丧，因为你会想，
who are you doing it for then like I'd
你到底是为了谁而做这一切？我愿意
[__] die for Mike do you know what I
为迈克付出一切，你明白我的意思吗？
mean like if if someone had if someone
如果有人
said I'm going to I've got to kick you
说，我要把你踢出
business but Mike stays I'd go like this
局，但迈克留下来，我会想，
this isn't really for me I guess it's
这真的不是为了我，而是为了他。但现在的情况是，这种情况
where that can't
不能
happen he enjoys it too much we love
发生，他太享受这一切了，我们都热爱这份工作。
doing this so it's interesting that
所以，这个假设很有意思，它
illuminates much of the reason why
揭示了
you're doing it in the first place
你最初做这一切的很多原因，
because the first thing you said was who
因为你首先问的就是“
am I doing it for then
我是为了谁而做这一切”。是的，
yeah but if I had asked you earlier who
但如果我早点问你，
you're doing this for you would I don't
你是为了谁而做这一切，你会说吗？我不
know if you would have said I'm doing it
知道你会不会说“我是
for Mike no I am I'm doing it for Mike
为了迈克而做”，不，我是为了迈克，
I'm doing it for the team I'm doing it
我是为了团队，我
for my family definitely but if the team
当然是为了我的家人。但如果
if the team leaves you're still going to
团队离开了，你还会
crack on yeah it's just a new team but
继续吗？是的，只是换了个团队。但
if Mike leaves if Mike if Mike leaves I
如果迈克离开了，如果迈克…… 如果Mike离开，我
don't know if I carry on that's so
不知道我是否还能继续下去，这个问题很难
answer I had a business partner and the
回答。我之前有个商业伙伴，
reason I asked that question is I
我问这个问题是因为我也有过
thought the same I thought one day I
同样的感受。有一天我设
played out my scenario that they quit
想了一下他们退出的情景，我记得当时我也在
and I remember thinking to myself the
想，
exact same thing who am I doing this for
我到底是为了谁而做这件事？但
then like we started this together so
我们是一起创立的，所以我们的
the mission is actually me and you
目标其实是携手
getting to the finish line and you get
走到最后。
excited when they get excited or like if
当他们兴奋的时候，你也会兴奋；或者
if Mike sends me a design that he's in
如果Mike发给我一个他很喜欢的设计，
love with and I'm like [__] hell yeah
我会觉得“卧槽，太棒了！”，
energy between you if that wasn't there
你们之间就有那种默契。如果这种默契消失了，那确实会很
anymore it yeah it would suck how
糟糕。
important do you think having a
你觉得有个
co-founder is I think massively I know
联合创始人有多重要？我觉得非常重要。我知道
earlier when you said you get lonely
你之前说过你会感到孤独，
like I think that is a major Block in
我觉得这能有效缓解
loneliness cuz he is always there um and
孤独感，因为他总是在我身边。
I
我
have like I I always have him to lean
总是可以依靠他，
into and I would never put pressure and
我永远不会给
stress on him in a personal way but I
他施加个人压力，但我
know he's there if that happened
知道如果真的发生什么，他会一直在我身边。
um so I think it's it's a massive thing
所以我觉得这非常重要。
but who you going to business with is
但是，和谁一起创业也是非常
another massive thing and like you've
重要的。 事情就是这样，你们必须
got to be completely different to each
完全不同，
other and even though we look the same
即使我们外表相似，看起来也一样，但我们本质上
and we seem the same like we are very
是
different people what have you learned
截然不同的人。你
from the bad people that you've hired
从那些你雇佣的、
the ones that didn't
不称职的人身上学到了什么？
work in terms of when I say that I
我说的是，
mean what have you learn is a bad
你学到了什么？
quality in someone to work with to build
与人共事、共同创业，或者与
employee um stuck in old ways and not
员工合作，有哪些不好的品质？比如固守旧观念，不愿接受
being open-minded to change I think a
改变。我认为
lot of people are very restrictive when
很多人非常保守，
especially if you're bringing someone
尤其是在你提拔比
higher up from them then some people
他们级别更高的人时，有些人
will always like backfire against that
总是会反噬自身，
and that's a bad quality and get it's a
这是一种不好的品质。我知道这是
human nature and I understand it and you
人之常情，我理解。你
can always try and like change the way
可以尝试改变
they think about things but if they're
他们的想法，但如果他们
not willing to accept that change
不愿意接受改变，
especially when you're in a growing
尤其是在一家快速发展的
company like there's some people and
公司里，有些人——
Spenny always tells me this there's some
斯潘尼总是跟我说——能
people that will take you to 50 mil and
带你达到5000万美元，有些人能带你
there's some people that'll take you to
达到
250 mil and there's some people take you
2.5亿美元，有些人能带你
to a billion and it won't be the same
达到10亿美元，但这些人不会是同一批
people and you've just got to accept
人。 你必须接受
that and you got to do everything you
这一点，你必须尽你所能去帮助
can for them people at that that time
他们，
however however far they go with the
无论他们当时对
brand I I actually had a conversation
品牌的发展有多大影响。
with a Founder the other day whose
前几天我和一位创始人聊过，他的
business I've just invested in and it's
公司我刚投资过，我们聊的内容跟你提到的
the exact same conversation that nobody
完全一样，只是似乎没人
seems to talk about because in both your
提起过。因为你我的
case and mine we both did the same thing
情况都一样，
we hired a bunch of young people yeah
我们都招了一批年轻人，他们可能是
were willing to come and work for us
愿意来我们公司工作的人，也
maybe manage yeah and then the business
可能是我们能管理的人。然后公司
grows and the problem you have is the
发展壮大，问题就来了：
next set of talent you need um to get
你需要下一批人才来帮
you up to the next rung in this in on
你提升到更高的层次，
ladder they need to come in above the
他们需要从那些
people that were there from the
从一
beginning yeah and the originals don't
开始就在公司的人之上加入。而老员工不
love that MH because that kind of blocks
喜欢这样，因为这会阻碍
their progression just that's what they
他们的发展，他们就是这么想的。
think that's what they think but no it's
但事实并非
not true is it because they can learn
如此，因为他们可以
from them things and then they can step
从这些人身上学习，然后他们也能
up it just takes more time or they
晋升，只是需要更多的时间，或者说，
they'll get more knowledge out of it if
如果这些人真的加入，他们会从中获得更多知识。
that person does come in but ego's
但是，人的自尊心作祟。
yeah ego get in the way and like I said
没错，自负确实会阻碍事情发展，就像我说的，
some people are they're not openminded
有些人就是不开明，
to that and they also very people get
而且很多人
comfortable they get comfortable in that
安于现状，不愿向
want anyone to report into and they
任何人汇报，也
don't want to do this and do that but
不愿意做这做那。但这
that's life
就是生活，对吧？
right what is um what's next for
嗯，
you this year yeah start of the Year
你今年的下一步计划是什么？嗯，年初吧？
isn't it I guess we're building out
我想我们正在拓展
women's wear in the brand we are opening
品牌的女装业务，今年会开
three stores this year which will be our
三家店。 这将是我们的
first stores we've not done a store yet
第一家实体店，我们之前还没有开过实体店。
um and it's something that we've wanted
嗯，这是我们多年来一直想做的事情，
to do for so many years but just finding
但一直在寻找
the right places and being in the right
合适的地点和
space for it why why stores because
空间。为什么是实体店呢？因为
people think that's going against the
人们认为这违背了
way that the world's going everything's
世界的发展
getting more digital course yeah and
趋势，一切都在变得更加数字化。当然，
that's what that's I think that's a
我认为这正是我们的
major advantage like same thing happened
优势所在。就像之前
in Co everyone pulled away from their
在科罗拉多州发生的那样，大家都停止了
Productions and stopped selling garments
生产，一段时间内停止了服装销售，
for a while whereas we were like okay we
而我们则想，好吧，我们就
will take everyone's production space
利用大家的生产空间，
and we'll start selling online and then
开始在线销售。然后
we made huge
我们与一些以前我们根本无法合作的工厂建立了密切的
relationships with factories that we
合作关系。
usually couldn't get in and now we're
现在，我们与
like the best in them factories and
这些工厂的合作非常成功，并且
doing everything the right way with them
与他们合作的方式也完全正确，
because we supported them during them
因为我们在疫情期间一直支持着他们。
times but for the for the store aspect
至于实体店，
it's like we have these communities all
我们在
over the globe where people want to be a
全球各地都有这样的社群，人们渴望成为我们
part of the brand and the showing up to
品牌的一份子，他们
run clubs and we'll go and do one in
会来参加我们的活动，比如在
Dubai or we'll do one in La like I want
迪拜或洛杉矶开一家。我希望
somewhere for them guys to be able to
为他们提供一个可以
come into the brand them guys and girls
融入我们品牌的场所，无论男女。
to come into the brand and be able to
走进品牌，能够
smell it and feel it and touch it and
闻到、感受到、触摸到它，这种体验
have it way more professional than than
远比
just walking into a store and seeing it
走进商店在
on a rail or see it on a shoe shelf so
货架或鞋架上看到它要专业得多。所以，我们的目标是
it's about creating an area where the
创造一个空间，让
community can come in and feel more of
社区成员能够更深入地感受
the brand and who we are and what we do
品牌，了解我们是谁，我们做什么，
and then hopefully roll that out
然后希望将这种体验推广到
globally and then 247 has a lot of focus
全球。247 今年是我们重点关注的领域，以前
this year usually it's just like a
通常只有
couple people in the building that are
几个人在
doing it and now we've got a full team
做，现在我们有一个完整的团队在负责，
working on that we're trying to expand
我们正在努力拓展业务。
that hopefully I'd like to open some
我希望能够开设一些
gyms with it um the concept for that is
健身房，这个计划
is maybe next year but not this year and
可能要到明年，但今年不会。
then I'm building another brand called
此外，我还在打造另一个品牌
Cadence um which is an electrolyte drink
Cadence，这是一款高
high sodium first ready to drink sodium
钠即饮电解质饮料，是市场上首款罐装高钠即饮饮料。
the past year and a half with a guy
过去一年半，我一直在和一位
called Ross out here and that that's
名叫 Ross 的伙伴合作开发这个项目。之所以会这样做，是
because going back to
因为早在
201920 when I started getting into
2019-2020 年，当我开始关注
fitness and lifestyle and health like
健身、生活方式和健康时，
electrolytes just became something that
电解质就成了我关注的重点。 我一直
I was consistently taking and I've not
坚持服用，
been sick one day since then and I've
从那以后就没生过病，
never had my energy levels drop and I've
精力也从未下降过，
never had bad sleep and not I don't get
睡眠也一直很好，现在也不再
headaches anymore and it just seems like
头痛了。感觉好像是
this the salt that's in there is what is
里面的盐分让我
causing like this constant stream of
持续
energy and it's supporting my workouts
精力充沛，它还能支持我的锻炼。
and I love flavored drinks so I thought
我喜欢有味饮料，所以我就想，为什么
why can't I make my own version of that
我不能自己做一款呢？
we did earlier last year
去年早些时候，我们和一家公司合作，做了个测试，结果发现
um and it seemed our customer really
顾客很
wanted it so I was like We'll build
喜欢。所以我就想，不如我们再创建
another brand and put it under that
一个品牌，把它放在这个品牌旗下，
umbrella and see how it goes what is the
看看效果如何。我的
goal here I think the goal is like I
目标是什么呢？我觉得，
mean just generally like with all of
总的来说，所有
this stuff like what's the goal I I want
这些事情的目标是什么？我希望
rep I want represent to
Represent
be a lifestyle and not a brand I want it
成为一种生活方式，而不仅仅是一个品牌。我希望它与众不同，我希望它
more than just clothes and I say that a
不仅仅关乎服装。我最近经常这么说，
lot recently but I just want it to not
但我希望它
just be about the clothes I want the
不仅仅是关于服装，我希望
clothes to be a byproduct
服装只是一个副产品。
why why not no one's really done that
为什么不呢？目前还没有人真正做到这一点，
yet everyone talks about brand but I
每个人都在谈论品牌。
mean what's the point like you know you
你知道，你
got you got the jinkx you got the the
拥有了Jinkx系列，拥有了
247 range you got the the sort of
247系列，拥有了那种
original um represent range what is the
原创的、嗯，代表系列，那么
finish line here that's the good thing I
终点线在哪里呢？好消息是，我
don't think there is one I don't think
认为没有终点，
there is a I don't think there's a limit
我认为它没有极限，
to what it can be and what this thing
它能发展成什么样子，这个
that started offers 25 screen printed
最初只提供25件丝网印刷
T-shirts can become over the next 100
T恤的品牌，在未来100年左右的时间里能发展成什么样子。
years or so but do you not sit around
但是，你难道不会
with Michael and go listen we'll get to
和迈克尔坐在一起，听着，我们赚到
two billion we'll sell it there and
20亿美元，然后把它卖掉，
we'll just get a couple of Yachts
再买几艘游艇吗？
no no like look at Ben Francis they got
不，不，看看本·弗朗西斯，他的
valued at a billion he's still in the
估值达到了10亿美元，他还在
business it's not it doesn't become
做生意。这不是
about the money right it's not about the
关于钱的问题，对吧？这不是关于
money it's about what you're actually
钱的问题，而是关于你真正
able to do and do some things different
能做什么，做一些与众不同的事情，
and like not be conventional and try and
不墨守成规，尝试一些别人
that's that no one's done you know why
没做过的事情。你知道，为什么
not and I ask these questions you know
不呢？我问这些问题，你知道，
I'm playing devil's advocate here
我是在唱反调。
because I think some people think that
因为我觉得有些人认为
end with entrepreneurship generally it's
创业只是达到目的的手段，通常来说确实如此。
like a means to an end yeah but when I
但是当我跟像
speak to entrepreneurs like you it's so
你这样的创业者交流时，很
clear that it's much more about the
明显，他们更看重的是
journey and the journey you're like it
过程，感觉
just seems like you probably want to die
你好像希望
on The Journey at some point yeah well
在某个阶段就此结束。是的，你
you're speaking to like a lot of
接触的都是
successful people and people that have
成功人士，都是在这个行业摸爬滚打了
been in it for a long time right you're
很久的人，对吧？你
not speaking to those guys that are
接触的不是那些在
walking around on the street saying I'm
大街上到处嚷嚷着“我要
going to build this and I'm going to
建个公司，
sell it in 3 years for six billion or
三年后卖六十亿”或者“
yeah yeah yeah this is this is my exit
这就是我的退出
strategy and they've just started they
策略”的人，他们才刚刚起步，从来不
never work no one ever that never works
工作，从来不为任何人工作，这种
of thinking you're talking to the people
想法纯属扯淡。你接触的是那些
that have really bought into their own
真正投入到自己
[__] brand and they're living it and
品牌中，
they're loving it and it's for forever I
热爱并践行它的人，我
guess it's a mission isn't it there yeah
想这会成为他们毕生的事业，对吧？是的，这就是
that's their mission you're that's kind
他们的使命，也是
of the tagline that I associate to you
我一直以来对他们的印象。
because you you post that a lot yeah is
因为你经常发帖问这个问题，是的，这是
it's it's a mission and there's
一种使命，而
something difference between a business
商业
and a mission that's clearly what You'
和使命之间是有区别的，这一点你很清楚。你擅长什么？
you good at are you good at
你擅长商业吗？我
business I'm good at understanding
擅长理解
business um but when you say good at
商业。嗯，但是你说擅长
business what do you
商业是什么意思？我的
mean I mean you can Define it yourself
意思是，你可以自己定义，
but I guess what people typically think
但我猜人们通常认为的
of as businesses like operations Finance
商业是指运营、财务
processes no I'm not I'm
流程之类的。不，我不擅长，一点也不擅长。
not not at all I think that's actually
我认为这对
will be really wonderful news to a lot
很多人来说实际上是个好消息，
of people because there's a lot of
因为很多
people out there that think you have to
人认为你必须
be good at business to own a business no
擅长商业才能拥有一家公司。不，
I think it's about starting off and just
我认为关键在于起步，一路
figuring things out along the way and
摸索，把那些
that you're not good at that are way
你不擅长但比
better than you would it as soon as we
你强得多的人安排到你不擅长的领域。我们一
started doing that that's when the
开始这样做，
business took
公司就发展起来了。
off George we have a closing tradition
乔治，我们这个播客有个结束的传统，上一位嘉宾会给下一位嘉宾
leaves a question for the next guest not
留一个问题，但不
knowing who they're going to be leaving
知道下一位嘉宾是谁。
it for the question that's been left for
留给你的问题
is what is something in your life that
是…… 生活中有什么事
you assume to be true but you haven't
你觉得是真的，但你还没
yet deeply
深入
questioned this is quite funny because
质疑过？这挺有意思的，因为
it's something that I'm really
我对这个话题很
interested in but like don't don't talk
感兴趣，但你很少谈论
about it a lot um I
它。嗯，我
guess whether like the aliens are
想说的是，外星人是否就在
us not what I was expecting you to say
我们中间。
no not at all and it's completely
这完全出乎我的意料，跟
different to what we've just talked
我们刚才聊的完全不一样。
about for the past however long but that
不过，我
really like interests me um the fact
真的很感兴趣。现在
that like there's all these different
各种各样的故事、
sto and conspiracies and things that are
阴谋论层出不穷，
going on constantly especially now more
尤其是在当下，比以往任何时候都更加如此。
than ever and I wonder if it would
我想知道，
change the world if one of the governing
如果某个管理
bodies or whoever it was actually came
机构或者其他什么人站出来
out and said yes this is this is this
说“是的，这就是外星人，
and these are with us I think it's just
他们就在我们身边”，世界会不会因此而改变？我觉得
amazing we're going into like the world
我们正在进入模拟、人工智能等等领域，这真是太神奇了。
out with chat GPT the other day Sora
前几天我看到了GPT聊天软件，
where they can create they could do text
他们可以用它创建文本
to video yeah and that's when I I saw
转视频。然后我看到了
the first reply to Sam alman's tweet
对Sam Alman推文的第一条回复，
said this is the technology that was
说……
used to create us and and it just
创造我们的技术让
wobbled my brain a little bit because I
我有点懵，因为我
thought now we're getting to a point
想到我们现在
where we've got these Apple Vision Pro
有了Apple Vision Pro
headsets and we're able to make video
头显，可以制作带
text and I'm looking at this woman in HD
文字的视频，而我眼前这个85岁左右的高清老妇人，竟然是
by typing a couple of words and you just
通过输入几个字生成的。你
assume any rate of
想象一下，如果技术以任何速度
improvement and eventually you get to
进步，最终你会得到一个与现实
the world real yeah reality yeah we
世界毫无二致的东西。没错，我们
might even be a video game I think
甚至可能变成了电子游戏。
there's I've heard Elon talk about this
我听埃隆·马斯克说过这话，
and he's like he talks about it he said
他说他谈论这个话题
so much that he's had to ban the
太多了，以至于不得不禁止
conversation right because you fall into
讨论，因为你会陷入
a little bit of a hole Yeah you you
一个有点混乱的境地。没错，你
literally have no idea who we are what
根本不知道我们是谁，
we're doing why we why we're here and
我们在做什么，为什么会在这里。是的，是否存在
yeah is there an alternate universe or
一个平行宇宙？或者
are we just living in someone else's
我们只是生活在别人的
head I don't know so interesting thank
脑海里？我不知道。真有趣。谢谢
you Georgia thank you for a number of
你，乔治亚，谢谢你，
reasons thank you for dressing me for
原因有很多。谢谢你
the last uh three years because um I
过去三年为我设计服装，因为我
think your clothes are the best no thank
觉得你的衣服是最棒的。 谢谢，
it's a very subjective thing but but in
这的确是很主观的事情，但就
terms of quality and consideration
质量和用心程度而言，
sometimes you can tell when someone has
有时你能看出一个人是否
gone the extra mile in a piece of work
在作品中倾注了额外的心血，对吧？几乎总是如此，
right pretty much always when they've
当他们从根本上
thought about things from first
思考问题，认真
principles they've really thought about
考虑每一个决定时，他们就会这么做。
represent has always been to me a brand
对我来说，Represent 一直都是一个深思熟虑的品牌。
um and it's different in every way as I
嗯，正如我
said from an endtoend experience it's
所说，从头到尾的体验来看，它
different and you can tell that the
与众不同。你能感受到这个
brand comes from somebody somewhere
品牌源自某个人的
heart right and you can you can tell the
内心，对吧？你也能
difference again with Brands where you
再次分辨出，有些品牌根本
know someone didn't really care about
不在乎
the process and they were maybe copying
过程，可能只是在模仿
something else and then there's this
其他东西，而
other brand called represent where it's
Represent 这个品牌则截然不同，它
clearly coming from someone somewhere
显然源自某个人的
heart and their own unique Vision that's
内心，拥有自己独特的愿景。这就是
why I've always loved the brand um and
我一直喜欢这个品牌的原因，也是
that's why I think you've been able to
我认为你们能够
cultivate this cult because there's
培养出如此忠实拥趸的原因，因为
something in humans where they can tell
人类有一种本能，能够分辨
the real from the not so real yeah they
真假。是的，他们能感受到，
can just feel it we can feel it and
我们也能感受到。这就是 Represent 一直以来所代表的，也是
and that's why I've always been so
我一直喜欢它的原因。 我一直很
fascinated by you and your brother um
欣赏你和你的兄弟，我是
and a huge supporter of both both of you
你们俩的忠实支持者。从
and on like a human level you're just
人性层面来说，你们俩都是非常棒的人，我很感激。我经常​​在
back all the time I go that guy's a
背后说，那家伙真是个
great guy he's just like a really nice
好人，他非常友善谦逊。
humble human being and on paper you know
你知道，从表面上看，
people might look and go he has a lot of
人们可能会觉得他有很多
reasons not to be yeah this guy looks
理由不成功，比如，这家伙看起来就像
an alien
外星人画出来的一样，但
like but but and he's got this
他确实拥有令人
incredible business but he's a really
惊叹的事业，而且他本人也非常
good human being and so is Michael so
好，迈克尔也是。所以，
thank you for the inspiration keep doing
谢谢你们的激励，继续做
what you're doing cuz the mission that
你们正在做的事情，因为
you're on is um inspiring many other
你们的使命正在激励许多其他
people to start missions of their own
人去开启他们自己的使命。是的，
yeah I think that's something that the
我认为这是这个
world needs a lot more of so I
世界非常需要的。所以我很
appreciate it thanks for having me on
感激，谢谢你们邀请我参加“
loved
Loved
[Music]
Music”节目。